[
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608446030496
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the most difficult part of being a photographer for you? ",
            "answer": "Holding the camera. LOL"
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "Tripod Camera"
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "Abe chod na, reload kaun karega bhai. Vo bhi 3 baar\n\nReload pe thank you page pe jaane ki koi zaroorat nahi hai.\nItni baar koi reload nahi karega kyuki."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608446753092
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608445866690
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608450678965
      }
    ],
    "username": "manan.agrawal2018@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 5,
    "contact_number": 8800647617,
    "first_name": "Manan",
    "last_name": "Agrawal",
    "registration": "18BCE0567"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the primary function of a critique of your design? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            To improve the overall design. "
          },
          {
            "question": "RGB is to ppi as CMYK is to _.\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Dots per inch "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "Yes, I have a 1 year experience in Designing, UI/UX and Video Editing\nSoftwares Used\nDesigning : Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator\nUI/UX : Adobe XD\nVideo Editing : Final Cut Pro X, Adobe After Effects"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "1. In PNG we could make the background of the image transparent but not in jpg\n\n2. PNG is of higher quality whereas JPG is of low quality "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the use of pen tab in illustrator?\n ",
            "answer": "It is ised to trace an image to make a vector of it or can be used to make illustrations. It is one the most important tool in Illustrator "
          },
          {
            "question": "State types of brushes in brush tool in illustrator. ",
            "answer": "Art, Scatter, Pattern, Calligraphic, Bristle"
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "In photoshop, select the layers which you want to merge and then right click on it click Merge layers"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "I have an interest in designing and I want to improve myself in it, if the design the required urgently I would hold on to my work that I would be doing currently and start working on the design."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "I always complete my work before the deadline, in my second and third semester I was a part of the design team of ISTE-VIT and I never missed a deadline.\nIf I'am not able to meet the deadline I would ask someone else from the design team to help me complete my work before deadline if that person is free."
          },
          {
            "question": "Attach any of your previous work (at least 1) in the attachment below. (can be Event\nposters, Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video Editing, etc.) [ADD A DRIVE LINK] ",
            "answer": "https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1K5fsavWrzyOpGLsUfzGSbn4Mj4MM7LDU?usp=sharing"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608455017191
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608453535541
      }
    ],
    "username": "aishaan.datt2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 919149492527,
    "first_name": "Aishaan",
    "last_name": "Datt",
    "registration": "19BCT0175"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "A prime lens ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Has a fixed focal length "
          },
          {
            "question": "What does the “bulb” mode in the camera do? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Keeps the shutter open indefinitely "
          },
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": "The vertical movement of a camera on its axis is called ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tilt "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the most difficult part of being a photographer for you? ",
            "answer": "For me the hardest part would be reviewing the hundreds and thousands of images after a shoot and finding that perfect picture. "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the advantage of having a full frame sensor over a crop sensor? ",
            "answer": "A full frame sensor can perform much better in low light conditions that is it can perform well even with high ISO."
          },
          {
            "question": " What is your favourite lens and why do you prefer it? ",
            "answer": "I like the 50mm lens because it has a wide aperture and is really good for portrait photography. "
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "I'm not sure about what equipment to use for long exposure in a bright lighting condition. But we can increase the aperture and decrease the ISO to get better results."
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "They r inversely proportional. When aperture is more depth of field is shallow and vice versa."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608446881073
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be stored in list1 and list2 if the following code is executed?\nList1=[‘a’,’b’,’c’]\nList1+=’de’\nList2=[1,2,3,4]\nList2+=10 ",
            "answer": "\n                                            [‘a’,’b’,’c’,’d’,’e’],error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608464106356
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608446188885
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608462903481
      }
    ],
    "username": "manishravi.varrier2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 97450356594,
    "first_name": "Manish",
    "last_name": "Varrier",
    "registration": "20BCI0181"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true for microcontrollers and microprocessors? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both contain processing unit "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "Arduino library"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "By changing thickness of wire or the material of wire."
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Fingerprint sensor, Gyroscope, and Light sensors."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447344731
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608446140753
      }
    ],
    "username": "swastikraj.behera2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8658510587,
    "first_name": "SWASTIK",
    "last_name": "BEHERA",
    "registration": "20BEC0710"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "ITS THE PROCESS OF REPEATUBG"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608449775014
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608448571603
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608449785026
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608452733077
      }
    ],
    "username": "ananyaalok.somani2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9769497680,
    "first_name": "Ananya",
    "last_name": "Somani",
    "registration": "20BIT0363 "
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "recursion is repeating the same function within the function. that is nested functions."
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": " a protected variable can be called by a function in the same  class .but cannot be directly called by another private function ."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608441820307
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How is a color scheme different from color selection? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Schemes are pairings of colors that work well together. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "yes,graphic designing in gimp editor"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "png is a higher quality compression with no image data loss id present. jpg are generally lower quality but faster to load"
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "i will think about how calm i would feel after finishing my work .which automatically motivates me to finish."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608461740495
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608440591232
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608461220973
      }
    ],
    "username": "vaishnavi.sabarish2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9447678841,
    "first_name": "Vaishnavi ",
    "last_name": "Sabarish ",
    "registration": "20BCE2230 "
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "yes by defining it in local space and it will remain private to that function only"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608439863105
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "we can advertise by using social media like instagrams, we could send regular mails regarding event details and benefits. we can even ask current attendes to bring their friends by telling them the benefits of event"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I would try to increase his interest first by giving him easy tasks to work so that he gains confidence and later he will develop his interest for more difficult tasks."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "I will  ask the event coordinator of another event if he can he can delay their event because our is a big and its impossible to shift now . else i would book another auditorium nearby and put a board outside of  last auditorium to guide people that event is shifted to different near by venue . for future i will take more care and will confirm 2-3 days before the event is scheduled."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I would divide the audience by their interest like if some just want to attend award function can come later those who have other interest can attend it at their time and can leave then."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "sponsor are important because they fund the event which is the most important factor for the event. i will keep in mind the type of sponsor by checking his history of sponsoring  like if someone sponsors only sport events so would contact him when i would organise a sports event."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would get from company b as they will tell the techniques how to grow as they are growing more rapidly . they might have better idea then company a . also the speaker from company b will cost less as they aren't much famous as of now."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "it is necessary in order to attract the audience we should introduce new and creative ideas in the event."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "We can publicize the sponsors product by giving it in our  event poster and also adding some qualities of it in all our promotions sent via mail or sms. In online mode we can add his product on our social media handles and on our website too."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "I will prepare for important topics of exam due tomorrow then can continue with the chapters work so that none of them suffers due to another."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will introduce some other concept like motivational movie and some question answer round to divert and engage audience in different tasks ."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I would try to request the team member is they can postpone it by some time because of time collapsing else i would attend the most important one and get the important points of other by their team members so that i don't miss the important things of any meeting."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "I will try to put my point of view and try to explain it from my view . if they still don't  agree then i will listen and understand the things from their point of view."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608452852201
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608438609003
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608451528081
      }
    ],
    "username": "harsh.rajpal2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 7015469345,
    "first_name": "Harsh",
    "last_name": "Rajpal",
    "registration": "20BCI0271"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true for microcontrollers and microprocessors? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both contain processing unit "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "yes we need to import eg ultrasonicTEP.LIB"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "LENGTH INCREASE, AREA DECREASE(SMALLER DIAMETER), HEATING"
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "WIFI LIBRARY"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "GPS , ACCELEROMETER , GYROSCOPE"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608469484586
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608468286593
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608469525772
      }
    ],
    "username": "gaurav.popli2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 9352226347,
    "first_name": "Gaurav",
    "last_name": "popli",
    "registration": "20BML0054"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "Ultrasonic library is a basic functionality library commonly used.\nAlso Hcsr04 has its own library for usage."
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "By changing the wire materials, increasing the thickness and length of the wire.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "They are used for grounding"
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "use a module like ESP8266"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Ambient light senseor\nProximity sensor\nGrroscope\nCompass\nHall effect\nfingerprint"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608441654309
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "Ultrasonic library is a basic functionality library commonly used.\nAlso Hcsr04 has its own library for usage."
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "By changing the wire materials, increasing the thickness and length of the wire.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "They are used for grounding"
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "use a module like ESP8266"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Ambient light senseor\nProximity sensor\nGrroscope\nCompass\nHall effect\nfingerprint"
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "Ultrasonic library is a basic functionality library commonly used.\nAlso Hcsr04 has its own library for usage."
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "By changing the wire materials, increasing the thickness and length of the wire.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "They are used for grounding"
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "use a module like ESP8266"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Ambient light senseor\nProximity sensor\nGrroscope\nCompass\nHall effect\nfingerprint"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608441654714
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608440517770
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608441687233
      }
    ],
    "username": "pragadeshwar.vishnu2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 7010045201,
    "first_name": "Pragadeshwar ",
    "last_name": "Vishnu",
    "registration": "20MCE0010"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445371947
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the primary function of a critique of your design? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            To improve the overall design. "
          },
          {
            "question": "RGB is to ppi as CMYK is to _.\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Dots per inch "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "BLENDER,GIMP,SKETCHBOOK"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "jpg uses lossy compression algorithm\nPNG uses lossless compression algorithm"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the use of pen tab in illustrator?\n ",
            "answer": "used to draw and to create anchor points"
          },
          {
            "question": "State types of brushes in brush tool in illustrator. ",
            "answer": "scatter brush,brittle,pattern,art,calligraphic"
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "there will be a option layer >merge layers and select the desired layers"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "to learn new things and improve the design skills\ni do my best"
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "i try my best to deliver my best"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608446090399
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "yes,HCSR04"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "WE NEED IT FOR CLOSING ELECTRICALCIRCUIT AND COMMON LOGIC REFERENCE THROUGH OUT THE CIRCUIT"
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "CONNECT RED WIRE TO VIN\nCONNECT BLACK WIRE TO GROUND\nCONNECT GREEN WIRE TO TX OF WIFE MODULE AND MICROCONTROLLER\nYELLOW WIRE TO RX OF WIFI MODULE AND MICROCONTOLLER"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "RX AND TX MUST BE FREE"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "GRAVITY,PROXIMITY,BAROMETER,GYROSCOPE,FINGERPRINT"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447230447
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "USE SOCIAL MEDIA,SPAM MAILS,USE CLUB MEMBERS TO POPULARIZE EVENTS"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "UNDERSTAND HIS SITUATION AND TRY TO WORK AS SOLO"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447472592
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608444167938
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608445406620
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608446111484
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608447284817
      }
    ],
    "username": "kavin.2019a@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 8,
    "contact_number": 6383039742,
    "first_name": "KAVIN",
    "last_name": "KUMAR",
    "registration": "19MIC0082"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608459900194
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "A prime lens ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Has a fixed focal length "
          },
          {
            "question": "What does the “bulb” mode in the camera do? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Keeps the shutter open indefinitely "
          },
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": "The vertical movement of a camera on its axis is called ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tilt "
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "a sturdy tripod and a camera that allows you to alter shutter speeds."
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "the wider the aperture, the shallower is the depth of field "
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "a sturdy tripod and a camera that allows you to alter shutter speeds."
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "the wider the aperture, the shallower is the depth of field "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608460273083
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "A prime lens ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Has a fixed focal length "
          },
          {
            "question": "What does the “bulb” mode in the camera do? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Keeps the shutter open indefinitely "
          },
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": "The vertical movement of a camera on its axis is called ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tilt "
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "a sturdy tripod and a camera that allows you to alter shutter speeds."
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "the wider the aperture, the shallower is the depth of field "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608460273092
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "A prime lens ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Has a fixed focal length "
          },
          {
            "question": "What does the “bulb” mode in the camera do? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Keeps the shutter open indefinitely "
          },
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": "The vertical movement of a camera on its axis is called ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tilt "
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "a sturdy tripod and a camera that allows you to alter shutter speeds."
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "the wider the aperture, the shallower is the depth of field "
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "a sturdy tripod and a camera that allows you to alter shutter speeds."
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "the wider the aperture, the shallower is the depth of field "
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "a sturdy tripod and a camera that allows you to alter shutter speeds."
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "the wider the aperture, the shallower is the depth of field "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608460273948
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608458696316
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608459917864
      }
    ],
    "username": "ananya.p2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 8618016916,
    "first_name": "Ananya",
    "last_name": "P",
    "registration": "20BCE2379"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608470299775
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608469093076
      }
    ],
    "username": "anitesh.2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 917319947726,
    "first_name": "Anitesh",
    "last_name": "Jha",
    "registration": "20BCI0210"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "void main()\n{\nfloat x = 0.1;\nif(x==0.1){\nprintf(“IETE-ISF”);\nprintf(“%f ”,x);\n}\nelse{\nprintf(“IETE”);\nprintf(“%d”,x);\n}\n}\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            IETE Junk Value "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608477484566
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1.Online events\n2.TED talks by speakers of the events\n3.Try to contact every person indivi"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I will keep patience and wait for that member to become comfortable working with me.I will try to adjust with that team member be a little extra cautious that he/she feels fine working with me after sometime.If this continues for long,I will simply ignore and focus on my own task.Atleast I tried convincing the person to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "I will talk with the auhorities to give the auditorium to us at a another convinent time slot.If not,other way out is talking to the event coordinator of the other event and find a common solution.Maybe we can organize the event together in shifts in the same time slot.Maybe we can also try to merge the event and make the event one uge success together.\nI will check on the time slot properly next time extra attentively and more number of times to make sure it doesnt happen again."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I will definitely speak up to the people to be patient. I will divide the people into slots and make a proper time slot division to each slot available.Also,the people waiting for their time can have some fun activites till their slot chance comes."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "The sponshorships are important for an event because of funds and attracting public.We need funds for an event.Also,if the sponsor is popular,then we can use its brand value to publicize our event even more.I will take in mind that the sponshership is trustworthy and genuine.Whether popular or not,it should have a good reputation in market."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I will get a speaker from company A.The reason being that:\n1.The company is famous.It will publicize our event that we are getting them to speak.\n2.The company is well established.The person speaking will definitely be having a great experience to share with our audience.\n3.Maybe more people will not be able to associate themselves with Company B speaker because it is still a start up and not many people are knowing of it."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "It depends on the situation.If I have sufficient time,I will try to be as unique and creative.But if the event deadline is really very close,then its better to go with standard method and try to make it as perfect as possible.We dont want any end moment troubles simply because we were thinking of unique ideas."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "We can get to speak or give a TED talk.We can print the event merchandise with their logos on it .We can also takes quizes based the idea of their startup.For exapmle,a startup of online stock market can have a quiz played by the people on stock markets."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "I will give equal weightage to both.Chapter's urgent work can be done during the evening shifts and for paper I can study well in advance.I can simply plan my schedule well."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will send the event back stage participants to keep the audience entertained.Till that time I will arrange for another speaker as soon as possible.I will try to keep the audience busy in some actvites till another speaker comes."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I would like to focus on only one club.I believe in dedicating my time to one proper assignment rather on focusing on both the things simultaneously. If I am still a part of two clubs,I will go with the meeting of the club in which I am needed more urgently or my presence is strongly required."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "I will go with voting.The idea having maximum votes whether be it my idea or someone else's,I will go with that point.If we 3 have completely diffferent opinions,I will try to convince the other two of that why my point is better or maybe try that we all 3 come up with a new idea 4th idea that we all agree upon."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608479039150
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608476280592
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608477536405
      }
    ],
    "username": "khushi.jain2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9624599767,
    "first_name": "Khushi ",
    "last_name": "Jain",
    "registration": "20BCE2664"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "recursion is a function where the function is called several times."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608450519289
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1) Can use social media to advertise as everyone uses it.\n2) Can seek the help of VIT officials to advertise.\n3) Can use contacts of some students and describe about it"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "first i will ask the reason behind his denial then i will try to solve it "
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "Just call them and say that we are gonna do it as online event so that meeting wont get cancelled and while booking a venue we should ensure that there are no other events take place"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "we can just allow the members upto the venue can hold and we can stream it on online so that others will also be able to watch"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "sponsors are the heart of an event, Because they provide money.\nwhile choosing a sponsor we should see the brand value of them. if they have good brand value then people will automatically watch our events. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would go with company B because if it is a fast growing startup then people will know the brand and the money which we are gonna give them also reduces."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "it is necessary to come up with a creative idea."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "during the event we can do some unique thing with that sponsor's product and we can say that this was done by this product. so it will be a good advertisement "
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "there is no kinda priority both are important its just upon us in managing time"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "the members in the club too have some knowledge in that domain. so i will ask the most knowledgeable person in the club to be a speaker."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "will skip one other than that no other way"
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "then just analyse and find which point is best suitable for our workshop and do it"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608451931150
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608449361808
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608450862223
      }
    ],
    "username": "aswin.mm2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9489526610,
    "first_name": "ASWIN",
    "last_name": "MM",
    "registration": "20BIT0049"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "By increasing the length and decreasing the radius of the wire, by ohm's law. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "To ground or short circuit"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "magnetic field sensor\ngyroscope"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608450067274
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "void main()\n{\nfloat x = 0.1;\nif(x==0.1){\nprintf(“IETE-ISF”);\nprintf(“%f ”,x);\n}\nelse{\nprintf(“IETE”);\nprintf(“%d”,x);\n}\n}\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            IETE Junk Value "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608450764709
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608440772721
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608449431587
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608450081376
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608450774930
      }
    ],
    "username": "gayatri.konduru2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 9100180575,
    "first_name": "Gayatri ",
    "last_name": "Konduru",
    "registration": "19BEC0494"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "It is basically a process in which a function calls itself directly or indirectly."
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "A protected variable cannot be accessed by users of the class but can be accessed inside the subclass so, private variable cannot be called."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608448336553
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608447130079
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608448373361
      }
    ],
    "username": "alka.rani2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 9334715657,
    "first_name": "Alka",
    "last_name": "Rani",
    "registration": "19BCI0004"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1) Organizing live session in teams or zoom\n2) Using Instagram to promote the events\n3) Introducing interesting memes or videos on the events and share it in social media platform like whats  app , instagram  "
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "Working in a team means cooperating and understanding everyone's idea , so if someone doesn't want to work with I will first try to know the reason what problem he/ she has and then if I think it is my fault then I will correct it and try my best to co-operate with him/her.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "If ever this kind of situation happens then I will try to contact an event manager who can give the details of the auditorium which are available at that time and which is close to the original auditorium also. Although the time is less but great ideas always strike at the most crucial time. \nI will get the proper bill immediately after I book the auditorium and the day before the event I will contact the manager to confirm my booking and whether everything is perfectly ready."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "If this kind of situation arrives then I will divide the members in two groups  and by doing this the program can be held smoothly and everyone can take part equally in it."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "For any event to be held in a proper manner we need adequate resources  for the smooth conduct of the event, if I need to approach any person for sponsorship I need to be first clear about what I actually want so that I can explain to the person about the event properly and also convince him. We can also say that it will be a kind of promotion for them also. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "An already developed company will tell about his past experience but a developing company will share his or her present development and how the company is progressing so I would choose Company B."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "Unique or interesting idea always attracts people so we should always proceed with creative ideas."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "By creating unique posts or attractive tags in online mode ."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "The main idea about management is BALANCE, so I will try my best to submit my paper as fast as possible and g\nthen give my full time to the club to complete the urgent call."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "If someone back's up for emergency so immediately I need to find someone from my team who is a good speaker to handle the event or if necessary I will do the necessary speaking if I don't get anyone."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "At that time I will select the club which has something more important to discuss ."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "We will bring out a common point in which we all agree or if I feel that my idea is not agreed by anyone then I will go with the majority choice."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608478372017
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "yes, I'll be importing the Arduino HC - SR04 Ultrasonic Sensor LIbrary from HC zip file"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "Increasing the length and by reducing the diameter"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "To connect wires to construct circuit and conjunction with breadboard and some wire."
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "connect both ESP's to the red wire\nconnect ESP's to ground\nConnect ESP's TX to UNO PIN 3"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608479743406
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the primary function of a critique of your design? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            To improve the overall design. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "NO I have no experience is graphics."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "JPG uses lossy  compression algorithm and image may loose some data whereas in png uses lossless compression algorithm and no image data is lost."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the use of pen tab in illustrator?\n ",
            "answer": "Pen tab is used for illustrating certain expression  it helps in giving precision to an image."
          },
          {
            "question": "State types of brushes in brush tool in illustrator. ",
            "answer": "Art Brushes\nPattern Brushes\nScatter Brushes"
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "PRESS F7 AND CLICK WINDOWS LAYERS\nSELECT LAYERS IN PHOTOSHOP TOGETHER , SELECT THE LAYERS YOU WANT TO MERGE \nSELECT THE LAYERS AND RIGHT CLICK AND PRESS MERGE LAYERS\nOR CLICK CTRL+E"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "I want to develop my skills in designing so if I need to do some design urgently I will do the basics skills in designing to do the task given."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "I will always remind myself about my goal which will keep me motivated and help to strive for better."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608483024062
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the primary function of a critique of your design? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            To improve the overall design. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "NO I have no experience is graphics."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "JPG uses lossy  compression algorithm and image may loose some data whereas in png uses lossless compression algorithm and no image data is lost."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the use of pen tab in illustrator?\n ",
            "answer": "Pen tab is used for illustrating certain expression  it helps in giving precision to an image."
          },
          {
            "question": "State types of brushes in brush tool in illustrator. ",
            "answer": "Art Brushes\nPattern Brushes\nScatter Brushes"
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "PRESS F7 AND CLICK WINDOWS LAYERS\nSELECT LAYERS IN PHOTOSHOP TOGETHER , SELECT THE LAYERS YOU WANT TO MERGE \nSELECT THE LAYERS AND RIGHT CLICK AND PRESS MERGE LAYERS\nOR CLICK CTRL+E"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "I want to develop my skills in designing so if I need to do some design urgently I will do the basics skills in designing to do the task given."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "I will always remind myself about my goal which will keep me motivated and help to strive for better."
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "NO I have no experience is graphics."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "JPG uses lossy  compression algorithm and image may loose some data whereas in png uses lossless compression algorithm and no image data is lost."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the use of pen tab in illustrator?\n ",
            "answer": "Pen tab is used for illustrating certain expression  it helps in giving precision to an image."
          },
          {
            "question": "State types of brushes in brush tool in illustrator. ",
            "answer": "Art Brushes\nPattern Brushes\nScatter Brushes"
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "PRESS F7 AND CLICK WINDOWS LAYERS\nSELECT LAYERS IN PHOTOSHOP TOGETHER , SELECT THE LAYERS YOU WANT TO MERGE \nSELECT THE LAYERS AND RIGHT CLICK AND PRESS MERGE LAYERS\nOR CLICK CTRL+E"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "I want to develop my skills in designing so if I need to do some design urgently I will do the basics skills in designing to do the task given."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "I will always remind myself about my goal which will keep me motivated and help to strive for better."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608483025205
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608476892181
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608478540362
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608482142543
      }
    ],
    "username": "mahek.poddar2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 7,
    "contact_number": 9366423605,
    "first_name": "Mahek",
    "last_name": "Poddar",
    "registration": "20BEC0556"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be stored in list1 and list2 if the following code is executed?\nList1=[‘a’,’b’,’c’]\nList1+=’de’\nList2=[1,2,3,4]\nList2+=10 ",
            "answer": "\n                                            [‘a’,’b’,’c’,’d’,’e’],error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "A function which calls itself is called recursion function"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "Yes, if its inside the same class"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608471267876
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "social media events and promotions,Social media giveaways. "
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If he/she doesn't want to work with me, I would ask them why and correct myself if mistake was on my part. Else i would take this issue to my head and have him replaced."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "I will beforehand make sure twice/thrice that the auditorium is booked for our event. In case if some confusion like this arises, I would ask the auditorium manager to take steps favorable to me else i would just apologize to everyone and make sure i was the one responsible for this mistake"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "i would close the registration portal for further registration, then i would talk with the venue manager to allow few extra seats."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsorships are helpful for crowd sourcing funds for organizing an event. So if an organization is somewhat similar to the event going, Then i would approach them"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "i would definitely go for Company B because it would be disrespectable for the speaker if i went for A"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "A creative twist should be given to a standard procedure, but if an idea seems exceptionally good and there's a high probability for it being a success, I would take a risk"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "By organizing social media campaigns which would promote that product/service indirectly, in a way it would not be annoying to the people following the page"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "I wouldn't go to the extend of making these two important things clash. I will arrange and schedule my work accordingly"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I would search for an immediate alternative speaker who has knowledge in that field, or i would apologize to the crowd and entertain them in a different way"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I wouldn't first of all be in a situation like that, in case i end up in a situation like that i will leave the club i don't have that much interest"
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "i would explain why my idea would work else, I would go with the majority opinion "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608474345492
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608470064393
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608473006393
      }
    ],
    "username": "avinaash.m2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 7305279133,
    "first_name": "Avinaash ",
    "last_name": "M",
    "registration": "20BDS0235"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "rseistance can be increased by elongating the wire by which thickness of cross section decreases which increases the resistance"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "arduino pins"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "gyroscope\nfinger print sensor\nbarometer"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608441700686
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608440692939
      }
    ],
    "username": "sohan.korimilli2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7904943088,
    "first_name": "sohan",
    "last_name": "korimilli",
    "registration": "20BME0228"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "repeated application of the alogorithm that handles a list of item"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "no."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608440851081
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the primary function of a critique of your design? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            To improve the overall design. "
          },
          {
            "question": "RGB is to ppi as CMYK is to _.\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Dots per inch "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "yes,power director"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "png has higher quality compression format\njpg has lower quality compression format"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the use of pen tab in illustrator?\n ",
            "answer": "to set stroke. it is the most powerful drawing tools. you can create path."
          },
          {
            "question": "State types of brushes in brush tool in illustrator. ",
            "answer": "calligraphic brushes\nscatter brush\nart brush\nbristle brush\netc"
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "turn on visibility\nshift+ctrl+alt+E"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "refering to previous designs and modifying previous designs"
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "promise myself a reward for doing the task. also strongly believe that hardwork pays off one way or the other"
          },
          {
            "question": "Attach any of your previous work (at least 1) in the attachment below. (can be Event\nposters, Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video Editing, etc.) [ADD A DRIVE LINK] ",
            "answer": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/19MQrsCRbablz5-xcjTsjtKOVpaM7YGNZ/view?usp=drivesdk"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608441927280
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "social media advertising\nthrough instagram, facebook etc\n                           conduct online programs or competition attracting the appropriate crowds.\n                               publicise it among family ad peers and asked their help to do the same\nask help of a flourishing venture with the advertisements.\n     "
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "conduct a vote whether to decide to remove me or the other person from the team and do so."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "its always important to have a backup plan,. so the back up auditorium will be used for the event \nand will execute the plan that was made for such a crucial times where every member will come around to help."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "either theassigned venue will be changed.\n\nor the event will be conducted in multiple days in the same venue.\n\nOr first come first serve method will be used till the limit of the venue is reached and then the rest of the registrations will have to watch the live telecast of the event."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "ensure the requirements of the event and how it is related to the sponsor .\nmake sure of the quality of the eventand ensure that the program will be conducted in the best way possible."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "Company A . For the event to be a success we need the more attention so having a well established speaker is the best choice."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "follow the standard  procedure including our unique and creative ideas."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "by distributing flyers \ndisplaying banners advertising the sponsor's product/services"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "depends on the weightage of the paper in gpa and how big the chapter work is and how it would benefit me or the chapter itself."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "have him conduct an online appearance at the event from the hospital. justifying the reason , depending on how big his medical situation is"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "decide based on how the club benefits me"
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "ill leave since they are more in number. "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608450044418
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608439790463
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608440865646
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608448555468
      }
    ],
    "username": "susan.shilbi2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 8590167490,
    "first_name": "Susan",
    "last_name": "Shilbi",
    "registration": "20MIC0006"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "it is a function that will call itself and repeat its program ubtil some condition is met to return a result"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608459565770
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "The vertical movement of a camera on its axis is called ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tilt "
          },
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": "A prime lens ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Has a fixed focal length "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the most difficult part of being a photographer for you? ",
            "answer": "Body steady maintenance for perfect shot"
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the advantage of having a full frame sensor over a crop sensor? ",
            "answer": "A dull frame sensor can provide a long range and better low/high light which gives higher quality image. and crop sensor is for cropping. So there is advantage of using full frame sensor"
          },
          {
            "question": " What is your favourite lens and why do you prefer it? ",
            "answer": "telephoto lens  that is a long focus lens that allows photographer to utilise focal length "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608460281507
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608458361629
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608459601432
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608459684508
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608460303290
      }
    ],
    "username": "asish.vishnu2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 9493571984,
    "first_name": "Asish",
    "last_name": "Vishnu",
    "registration": "20BCE0879"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "recursion is function that calls itself until boundary condition is met"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608439987159
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608438770602
      }
    ],
    "username": "nitish.js2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7010365232,
    "first_name": "Nitish",
    "last_name": "J S",
    "registration": "20BCE0182"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Calling a function inside itself"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "No"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447417796
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608446247928
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608447442592
      }
    ],
    "username": "loganathana.n2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 8248987618,
    "first_name": "LOGANATHAN ",
    "last_name": "A N",
    "registration": "19BCT0081"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "HC-SR04"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "Replace resistance with one of the higher value\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "This helps to isolate inductive noise from going across the arduino circuitry"
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "arduino helps it easier and make work smoothly"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "HC--05"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "proximity sensor\ngyroscope\nfinngerprint sensor\n"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608439947870
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608438741893
      }
    ],
    "username": "utsav.mishra2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9122606638,
    "first_name": "Utsav",
    "last_name": "Mishra",
    "registration": "20BEC0200"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recursion is used to call a function again without calling it repeatedly"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447419765
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "I would rate myself 9/10. I feel that I am a proficient English speaker and writer. I have a good command over the language and express myself diligently. I have also freelanced in article and content writing.\nI have also written a number of articles for my school monthly magazine."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "In my opinion, 'writing' is an art. It requires more imagination and thoughts than to simply put on a few words together. Writing brings me satisfaction and opens the chest of ideas. Writing improves my creativity and gives me the ability to think more logically and structurally."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "Technology is just a ten-letter word, but has had the ability to change the face of anything and everything. It has given us common men to explore limitless possibilities and bring about changes that can make this earth a better place to live.\nTechnology in the recent times has seen changes like no other thing has ever seen on this planet, and the 21st century has given this beast its wings. Technology comes from the Greek words for 'applied arts' and in this century we have seen just that. Now technology is more available to the people rather than just big industrial machines and rockets. Tech has allowed people to connect on a whole new level. \nHence, this word has the potential shake the world and make Earthians  lazier than  ever!\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "\"Learn to make a machine learn!\""
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "My best accomplishment yet, was to become the \"HEAD BOY\" of my school. I was the head boy of my school for the academic session of 2017-18. I learned to be responsible and accountable for my duties and actions. It has taught me a lot in life. It ma"
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "Organization and Planning are the only ways to survive in an environment where there is enough competition to kill your motivation to work.\nEvery morning, I make a to-do list of the things I need to get done and then, I prioritize them according to my needs and deadlines. Then, I feed everthing into my calender"
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "IETE's editorial team can give the power to express myself sitting in front of a computer and give me the opportunity to talk about something I'm most interested in \"TECH\". "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608449388122
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608446195881
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608447584921
      }
    ],
    "username": "arhitbose.tagore2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9110389277,
    "first_name": "Arhit",
    "last_name": "Bose Tagore",
    "registration": "20BCE2150"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608448010171
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608447757013
      }
    ],
    "username": "tanay.raj2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 919503614780,
    "first_name": "Tanay",
    "last_name": "Raj",
    "registration": "19BBS0018"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "HC-SR04"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "BY USING LONGER WIRES"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "BECAUSE EVERY SENSOR NEEDDS TO BE CONNECTED TO A SINGLE PIN THAT IS GND PIN"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "TX AND RX"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "GRAVITY SENSOR,TEMPERATURE SENSORS,MOTION SENSORS"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608440497068
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "HC-SR04"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "BY USING LONGER WIRES"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "BECAUSE EVERY SENSOR NEEDDS TO BE CONNECTED TO A SINGLE PIN THAT IS GND PIN"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "TX AND RX"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "GRAVITY SENSOR,TEMPERATURE SENSORS,MOTION SENSORS"
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "HC-SR04"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "BY USING LONGER WIRES"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "BECAUSE EVERY SENSOR NEEDDS TO BE CONNECTED TO A SINGLE PIN THAT IS GND PIN"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "TX AND RX"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "GRAVITY SENSOR,TEMPERATURE SENSORS,MOTION SENSORS"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608440498287
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "USING SOCIAL MEDIA WOULD BE AN BEST SUGGESTION FOR THAT OR ORGANISING AN PRIZE MONEY COMPETITION WOULD DIRECTLY GRAB ATTENTION OF THE STUDENTS"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I WOULD MAKE HIM REALISE HIS POTENTIAL THAT WHAT HE CAN DO OR BY OFFERING A RESPECTABLE POST."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "I WILL MAKE MY TEAM READY THAT WHENEVER THE ANOTHER PROGRAMME IS FINISHED I WOULD DIRECTLY MAKE MY SETUP THERE AND I WILL MAKE ALL THE NECESSARY ARRANGEMENTS WHILE THE ANOTHER FUNCTION IS GOING ON AND IT WILL TAKE JUST 10 MINS WHEN THE PROGRAMME GETS OVER MY WHOLE TEAM WILL START DECORATING THE STAGE. AND IN ORDER TO AVOID THE FURTHER MISUNDERSTANDING I WILL DRAT A COMPLAIN AGAINST THE MANAGER OF THE AUDITORIUM THATTHIS DOSENT TAKES PLACE AGAIN"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I WOULD BE MAKING DIFFRENT DIFFERENT SHIFTS FOR THAT"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "THAT THE SPONSER MUST PROVIDE BUDGET."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I WOULD LIKE TO INVITE BOTH THE COMPANY OWNERS BECAUSE COMAPANY OWNER OF A WILL DISCUSS HIS EXPERIENCE OF GETTING SUCCESS.AND OWNER OF COMAPANY B WILL SHARE THE EXPEREINCE THAT HOW DO WE GO THROUGH HARD TIMES"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "YES IT IS IMPORTANT TO COME UP WITH THE UNIQUE IDEA BECAUSE WE HAVE THINK OUT OF THE BOX IN ORDER TO MAKE OUR PROGRAMME DIFFERENT"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "IN ONLINE MODE BECAUSE IT HAS POTENTIAL TO SHARE GLOBALLY WITHIN LESS AMOUNT OF TIME"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "CHAPTERS URGENT WORK"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "WE WILL TELL ANY OTHER SPEAKER TO SPEAK AND WILL CONVEY THE MEDICAL EMERGENCY OF THE SPEAKER TO THE AUDIENCE"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I WOULD HAVE TO TAKE LEAVE FROM ONE MEETING"
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "I WILL GO WITH THE MAJORITY IN ORDER TO MAKE BALANCE OF THE WORKSHOP"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608441606782
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "USING SOCIAL MEDIA WOULD BE AN BEST SUGGESTION FOR THAT OR ORGANISING AN PRIZE MONEY COMPETITION WOULD DIRECTLY GRAB ATTENTION OF THE STUDENTS"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I WOULD MAKE HIM REALISE HIS POTENTIAL THAT WHAT HE CAN DO OR BY OFFERING A RESPECTABLE POST."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "I WILL MAKE MY TEAM READY THAT WHENEVER THE ANOTHER PROGRAMME IS FINISHED I WOULD DIRECTLY MAKE MY SETUP THERE AND I WILL MAKE ALL THE NECESSARY ARRANGEMENTS WHILE THE ANOTHER FUNCTION IS GOING ON AND IT WILL TAKE JUST 10 MINS WHEN THE PROGRAMME GETS OVER MY WHOLE TEAM WILL START DECORATING THE STAGE. AND IN ORDER TO AVOID THE FURTHER MISUNDERSTANDING I WILL DRAT A COMPLAIN AGAINST THE MANAGER OF THE AUDITORIUM THATTHIS DOSENT TAKES PLACE AGAIN"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I WOULD BE MAKING DIFFRENT DIFFERENT SHIFTS FOR THAT"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "THAT THE SPONSER MUST PROVIDE BUDGET."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I WOULD LIKE TO INVITE BOTH THE COMPANY OWNERS BECAUSE COMAPANY OWNER OF A WILL DISCUSS HIS EXPERIENCE OF GETTING SUCCESS.AND OWNER OF COMAPANY B WILL SHARE THE EXPEREINCE THAT HOW DO WE GO THROUGH HARD TIMES"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "YES IT IS IMPORTANT TO COME UP WITH THE UNIQUE IDEA BECAUSE WE HAVE THINK OUT OF THE BOX IN ORDER TO MAKE OUR PROGRAMME DIFFERENT"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "IN ONLINE MODE BECAUSE IT HAS POTENTIAL TO SHARE GLOBALLY WITHIN LESS AMOUNT OF TIME"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "CHAPTERS URGENT WORK"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "WE WILL TELL ANY OTHER SPEAKER TO SPEAK AND WILL CONVEY THE MEDICAL EMERGENCY OF THE SPEAKER TO THE AUDIENCE"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I WOULD HAVE TO TAKE LEAVE FROM ONE MEETING"
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "I WILL GO WITH THE MAJORITY IN ORDER TO MAKE BALANCE OF THE WORKSHOP"
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "USING SOCIAL MEDIA WOULD BE AN BEST SUGGESTION FOR THAT OR ORGANISING AN PRIZE MONEY COMPETITION WOULD DIRECTLY GRAB ATTENTION OF THE STUDENTS"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I WOULD MAKE HIM REALISE HIS POTENTIAL THAT WHAT HE CAN DO OR BY OFFERING A RESPECTABLE POST."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "I WILL MAKE MY TEAM READY THAT WHENEVER THE ANOTHER PROGRAMME IS FINISHED I WOULD DIRECTLY MAKE MY SETUP THERE AND I WILL MAKE ALL THE NECESSARY ARRANGEMENTS WHILE THE ANOTHER FUNCTION IS GOING ON AND IT WILL TAKE JUST 10 MINS WHEN THE PROGRAMME GETS OVER MY WHOLE TEAM WILL START DECORATING THE STAGE. AND IN ORDER TO AVOID THE FURTHER MISUNDERSTANDING I WILL DRAT A COMPLAIN AGAINST THE MANAGER OF THE AUDITORIUM THATTHIS DOSENT TAKES PLACE AGAIN"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I WOULD BE MAKING DIFFRENT DIFFERENT SHIFTS FOR THAT"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "THAT THE SPONSER MUST PROVIDE BUDGET."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I WOULD LIKE TO INVITE BOTH THE COMPANY OWNERS BECAUSE COMAPANY OWNER OF A WILL DISCUSS HIS EXPERIENCE OF GETTING SUCCESS.AND OWNER OF COMAPANY B WILL SHARE THE EXPEREINCE THAT HOW DO WE GO THROUGH HARD TIMES"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "YES IT IS IMPORTANT TO COME UP WITH THE UNIQUE IDEA BECAUSE WE HAVE THINK OUT OF THE BOX IN ORDER TO MAKE OUR PROGRAMME DIFFERENT"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "IN ONLINE MODE BECAUSE IT HAS POTENTIAL TO SHARE GLOBALLY WITHIN LESS AMOUNT OF TIME"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "CHAPTERS URGENT WORK"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "WE WILL TELL ANY OTHER SPEAKER TO SPEAK AND WILL CONVEY THE MEDICAL EMERGENCY OF THE SPEAKER TO THE AUDIENCE"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I WOULD HAVE TO TAKE LEAVE FROM ONE MEETING"
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "I WILL GO WITH THE MAJORITY IN ORDER TO MAKE BALANCE OF THE WORKSHOP"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608441608414
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608439693352
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608440554076
      }
    ],
    "username": "yuvrajsingh.deora2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 6376179619,
    "first_name": "YUVRAJ",
    "last_name": "singh",
    "registration": "20MIS0198"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "By using a longer or thin wire"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Fingerprint sensor, Gyroscope, Ambient Light sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608440889863
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608439886941
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608440904797
      }
    ],
    "username": "raunak.raj2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 7984944138,
    "first_name": "Raunak",
    "last_name": "Raj",
    "registration": "20BEE0123"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "Arduino HC-SR04 Ultrasonic Sensor Library"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "Increasing the length of the wire and smaller diameter"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "To close the electrical circuit and provide a common logic throughout the circuit"
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "For simple connectivity across any interface"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "13"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Proximity sensor\nLight Sensor\nFingerprint Sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608439813891
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608438647044
      }
    ],
    "username": "saksham.kapoor2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7073282716,
    "first_name": "Saksham",
    "last_name": "kapoor",
    "registration": "20MBE0014"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "a defined function can call itself , eg find your way home if you are at home stop moving"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "no, cant be accessed by a class u need a subclass that inherits from the class"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608439867016
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608438649944
      }
    ],
    "username": "devang.garg2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 917728041169,
    "first_name": "Devang",
    "last_name": "Garg",
    "registration": "20BCI0115"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "calling a func inside the same func "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608449123953
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "calling a func inside the same func "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "calling a func inside the same func "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608449124653
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608447920367
      }
    ],
    "username": "ganesh.sahu2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 918979891106,
    "first_name": "Ganesh",
    "last_name": "Sahu",
    "registration": "20BEE0124 "
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1) Instagram pages. Maybe the most common method but with proper quality and schedule of posts can make a huge difference.\n\n2) YouTube. Uploading YouTube videos of trailers and behind the scenes go a long way in showing students what the event is all about.\n\n3)Discord. I certainly have started using Discord a lot since the start of the lockdown and a dedicated server to the event with proper bots to give notifications and updates will certainly get students' attention."
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "Talk to the individual to put the team before personal differences. The team's success should be the ultimate goal.\nI'd also be inclusive and try to work with him more, so that arguments may be set aside.\nEvery team member has individual roles, so if our roles do not coincide, it'll be best to avoid the person."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "There are 2 ways this situation will go-\n1) We book another auditorium or do an open venue event. It will be difficult to organise but somehow manageable.\n\n2)We convince the other 2 parties to postpone their event.\n\nTo make sure something like this never happens, I will-\n\n1) Keep constant checks on the venue and inquire on a timely basis.\n\n2) Be organised and keep everything ready incase something wrong happens."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I'd suggest a first cum first serve basis for such a situation."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for an event as they give us the necessary funding to execute the event smoothly.\nThe key factors to look in mind while looking for a sponsor is-\n1) They should set their terms clearly. Sponsors that change their terms indecisively are a huge hassle.\n2) Their goals should coincide with the key outcomes of the event."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I'll get a speaker from company B. While bringing a speaker from company A might help us get more traction to the event, the speaker from company B will have more innovative and motivational ideas to share."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "A mix of both. While standard procedures help us to organise an event efficiently, unique and creative ideas give the event refreshing angles, which are very important to capture the audience."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "1) Posters. Including brand names and products in the posters for the event will help in publicising the brand a lot\n\n2) If it is a food related brand, stalls may be opened up. There's no better way to advertise a product than letting people try it."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "That depends on the context. If the paper plays a relatively huge role in my grade, I'd study for the paper more. But chapter's work will be more exciting, so I would prefer to work for the chapter on most occasions."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "This situation would be very tough to handle. Instead of keeping the participants waiting, I'd rather give them the straight fact and organise something else for that time frame. It will surely disappoint them though."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "Prioritise. It will depend on the agenda of the meetings on the basis of which I will decide which to attend. I can always get the key points of the other meeting later."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "1) Reach middle ground. We can work out a point that may work for all of us.\n\n2) Take an unbiased opinion from someone else."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608440338885
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recursion is when we call a function within itself. It is repeating items in a self similar way."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608441580191
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recursion is when we call a function within itself. It is repeating items in a self similar way."
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recursion is when we call a function within itself. It is repeating items in a self similar way."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608441580454
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608438825792
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608440407391
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608441648519
      }
    ],
    "username": "ayushmant.bharadwaj2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 9958493981,
    "first_name": "Ayushmant",
    "last_name": "Bharadwaj",
    "registration": "20BCE0648"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "by lowering the voltage or by increasing the current"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "its used to ground the circuit"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "rx pin and tx pin"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "accelerometer sensor, fingerprint sensor, IR sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608482489839
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608481274725
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608482511839
      }
    ],
    "username": "sarathkumar.k2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 8220611041,
    "first_name": "Sarath",
    "last_name": "Kumar",
    "registration": "20BEC0422"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Gyro sensor, proximity sensor, Accelerometer sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608439783043
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608439045909
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608439806344
      }
    ],
    "username": "nandagiririshi.rigved2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 7899320284,
    "first_name": "Rishi",
    "last_name": "Rigved",
    "registration": "20BEC0384"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "recursion is the the method of finding solutions to a problem by explaining it in terms of smaller, different versions itself.\n\nthe problem can be defined in its own terms.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "no\n"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608440110078
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "RGB is to ppi as CMYK is to _.\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Dots per inch "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "yes, imovie, audacity, apple clips, linea sketch"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "compression is jpg is lossy whereas it is lossless in png"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the use of pen tab in illustrator?\n ",
            "answer": "it is used just liek a pen and can be used to draw almots anythig , from lines to figures ,etc\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "State types of brushes in brush tool in illustrator. ",
            "answer": "art, bristle, scatter, pattern, calligraphic"
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "layers>merge layers"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "sketch them and make digital art designs for the team. the design team is fun and i will enjoy working for the team. "
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "This chapters work adds to my resume, looking at an empty resume will motivate me. this is something i want to do, i will never not be in the mood."
          },
          {
            "question": "Attach any of your previous work (at least 1) in the attachment below. (can be Event\nposters, Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video Editing, etc.) [ADD A DRIVE LINK] ",
            "answer": "wont let me move out of tab to copy and select link"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608440672033
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608438914420
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608440135744
      }
    ],
    "username": "tushar.singh2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 7303860645,
    "first_name": "tushar ",
    "last_name": "singh",
    "registration": "20BCT0197"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "You can tell some of the professors to tell students in the class about the events or at least tell them try to take part in this.\nthe university has given mail id to all the students so sending mail about the event can help also.\nthe Instagram page where people post their profile and tell their intro sometimes on the stories events should be given so that it may help a lot because 90% of them are on social media"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "the team leader would tell and it would be done on the basis of majority as only of them doesn't want to work and that person who doesn't want to work also doesn't have any other option he has to work with me because the teams are not decided so its better if he accepts it as soon as possible so we can focus more on the work."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "firstly I will go to the person who gave us the auditorium and tell how could he do this then as it was his fault and there is no other option that guy who gives the auditorium , me , and the other person whos event was colliding with me would work as fast as possible to find one more auditorium. To prevent this before the main event a day before and also a week before there should be certain reminder or would like to cross check if there is some collision or some fault so that nothing could go wrong"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Then I would like to do it in a certain batch. For eg. there are 2000 registrations and it exceeded by 500. so i would like to do it in 4 batches 10-12 first 500, 12-2 500-1000 and so on. In this way smoothly event can be conducted."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for event because it helps in reaching higher audience it also gives finances and it also has an brand image to the event. I would see it should be popular among teens so that our audience is based on teens then it would bring attention to it and it also could aid our finances."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "company b because his business is growing rapidly and at this time sometimes that also doesn't work due to many competitors in the market. they may also inspire people how they had the courage to do it. "
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "A  unique or creative idea would be different overall because and that would gather attention it is due to the fact it people sometimes get bored from the same old things but people still go."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "In an online mode i would send it to the watsapp groups instagram page and request the university to send it to students through vit mail"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "i would like to do a paper due tomorrow first and then chapter's urgent work if the chapter's urgent work is not big then i would that first and sometimes while doing the paper due tomorrow we still take breaks in that break i may do the chapter urgent work. I may even try to tell a friend to do the paper."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I would tell one of my co worker to do the work of the speaker as the speech would already be prepared."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I would like to see which club is better for me and helps me a lot and would go in that club."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "we would make a list of pros and cons and the one with the higher pros would be our final decision."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608440586085
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608439039038
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608440904080
      }
    ],
    "username": "somay.vaidh2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 9867418956,
    "first_name": "somay ",
    "last_name": "vaidh",
    "registration": "20bce2805"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608480592918
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608439282322
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608479587695
      }
    ],
    "username": "kaushiksanjay.prabha2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 9148645075,
    "first_name": "Kaushik",
    "last_name": "Sanjay Prabhakar",
    "registration": "20BCE0635"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be stored in list1 and list2 if the following code is executed?\nList1=[‘a’,’b’,’c’]\nList1+=’de’\nList2=[1,2,3,4]\nList2+=10 ",
            "answer": "\n                                            [‘a’,’b’,’c’,’d’,’e’],error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "DEFINING A PROBLEM IN SIMPLER TERMS\n"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608440660785
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608439412616
      }
    ],
    "username": "mohit.banka2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8757635668,
    "first_name": "Mohit",
    "last_name": "Banka",
    "registration": "20BEC0224"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608440971789
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608439706858
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608440992181
      }
    ],
    "username": "gayathrinandhana.m2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 8838685188,
    "first_name": "Gayathri ",
    "last_name": "Nandhana ",
    "registration": "20BCE2277 "
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What shutter speed would you use to take a panning shot? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1/30 "
          },
          {
            "question": "A prime lens ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Has a fixed focal length "
          },
          {
            "question": "What does the “bulb” mode in the camera do? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Keeps the shutter open indefinitely "
          },
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": "The vertical movement of a camera on its axis is called ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tilt "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the most difficult part of being a photographer for you? ",
            "answer": "For me, as of now I am just a beginner with some really basic knowledge and for me its really important to notice a particular movement and capture it the same way I see it and want people to see it. I want anyone who is watching it to know what I saw and what they wish they had seen."
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the advantage of having a full frame sensor over a crop sensor? ",
            "answer": "No idea about it. "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is your favourite lens and why do you prefer it? ",
            "answer": "I myself like taking pictures of people as in portraits or some really good flowers. I am not so good with landscapes so I mostly prefer prime lens. Which works quite well for me during the time I take pics."
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "Maybe a Tripod so that there isnt any blur in the image we click."
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "A larger aperture leads to a shallow depth of field."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608440888598
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608440324643
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608440931010
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608441136347
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608441156390
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608441638828
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608441660739
      }
    ],
    "username": "karthiksrinivas.b2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 7,
    "contact_number": 6302539984,
    "first_name": "Karthik",
    "last_name": "Srinivas",
    "registration": "20BCI0124"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1) social media being the most effective option.\n2) gather some juniors and give them the opportunity to become a part of this club/chapter by bringing people for the event which develops a chain of action.\n3) gather some really heavy name sponsors and event partners or welcome a special guest from the movie industry to lure the students."
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I will ask the reason and try to mend if possible and if he/she still doesn't want to work then I'll help him to get into another team.\n\nActually I have a very friendly nature so this won't be a possible scenario."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "everyone will be willing to help in this case and I think that the coordinator of other event will be happy to assist in this case and try to shorten the time of his/her event.This will enable very healthy future relations with that club/chapter.\n\nTo make sure that this never happens we'll have to confirm that the booking was successful at the specified timing and mistakes do happen so not to worry about them.\nwe should just learn to handle them well....."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "either arrange a new venue with more capacity and send out emails or texts if the venue is changed, in order to keep them informed.\nother than that I don't think that we have any option because if we cancel their registrations then it won't be good for the image of club/chapter and also the registrations that were cancelled won't participate from next time due to bad managing skills."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are very crucial bcoz money is required for every event,the venue booking,certificates,medals or prizes .So sponsors are important for every event"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "B bcoz it is well growing startup so we have better opportunity at having a better speaker.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "Most of the time we should go with the standard protocol but coming up with an unique idea is also necessary and sometimes we should organize these events also"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "ratings(google and other)\nany web site creation\nor app dev\nsocial media"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "first chapter and then paper\nand i know what u guys will say in this question which is that it should be vice versa."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "tell them the truth and reorganise the event"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "catch up with other fellow friends and ask if something was important discussed"
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "we will go with the majority as it is the best thing possible"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608468899853
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608473049815
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608473049833
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608473050063
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608473050564
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608473050935
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608473050945
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608473052592
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608473052604
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "A prime lens ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Has a fixed focal length "
          },
          {
            "question": "What does the “bulb” mode in the camera do? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Keeps the shutter open indefinitely "
          },
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": "The vertical movement of a camera on its axis is called ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tilt "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608473245473
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608467499846
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608472070603
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608473082643
      }
    ],
    "username": "mrigank.sachan2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 13,
    "contact_number": 9721539191,
    "first_name": "Mrigank",
    "last_name": "Sachan",
    "registration": "19BDS0050"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be stored in list1 and list2 if the following code is executed?\nList1=[‘a’,’b’,’c’]\nList1+=’de’\nList2=[1,2,3,4]\nList2+=10 ",
            "answer": "\n                                            [‘a’,’b’,’c’,’d’,’e’],error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Function calling itself "
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "Yes"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608441952422
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1) Posting the events and its related info in Social Media(i.e  Facebook, instagram etc) \n2) Allowing the student to register immediately after seeing the event post by providing a registration link. So that we can able to get his mobile number and phone number, to track him through Whatsapp.\n3) Keeping the event's post in WhatsApp status and forwarding the messages in all the groups."
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I Will ask that specific team member personally about his/her problems and discomforts with me.\nAfter analyzing his problem will try to convenience him/her by telling the merits of being in this club.\nAl-over its all a teamwork, so all the team member should have a healthy relationship to proceed further."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "Will book the auditorium and specify the duration of the event. I will also ask for the confirmation from the auditorium authorities stating that in the specified event interval no other events should take part.\n\nWill ask to book the auditorium before an hour so as to handle these kind of issues"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "First of all , I will not even proceed the registration process if the registration exceeds the assigned value.\nIf so, the strength is increased will conduct the event batch wise."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial since they will provide the entire fund for the event to occur.\nWill prepare a list of the overall cost for the event.\nAnd also mention of allocating some extra funds in situations of insufficient capital.\nWill adopt various advertisement strategies to brand their name."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "from Company B, since a speaker from start-up company knows very well the struggles and hard-ships of the company in the initial stage.\nDefinitely, he will be a great motivator for the students"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "Unique idea and creative ideas will always win"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "In online mode, we can use social media(insta's and fb's)\nIn offline mode, we can provide company-related magazines and stickers to the attending student."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Chapters urgent work will be the 1st priority,"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "Will try to step first and manage the situation. \nyet a difficult task, "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608448365733
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608440766612
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608446863238
      }
    ],
    "username": "prashanth.2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9003075249,
    "first_name": "Prashanth",
    "last_name": "S",
    "registration": "19MID0020"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608441953769
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1) Posting the events in frequently used social media\n2) Making a small clip within a minute comprising of all the achievements done by our club people and forwarding in regular interval of time to trigger their eagerness.\n3)Reveal our identity to our fellowmates &classmates and make them to develop hope with us and make them to feel that then can also achieve"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "1) Explain the situatuion & health of a team to him/her that not to be selfish which affect our team progress/prosperity . \n2) I will applogize him i it was my mistake and console him \n3) Convience him to do our work for the team first personally ."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "I try to build a healthy conversation with that event cordinator and convience that second coondinator how important this is and how we work hard for this to be co-ordinated and ask him to postponed his event for some time if it is possible . besides i will try to complete our event as soon as possible & then handle auditorium ... As a precaution i will ask the manager and confirms that nothing will clash with our event."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I try to make  extra seats  for them to sit . \nif possible , try to arrange a projector to live stream the event in nearby places.."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "first we have to decide that in what way that the organization will be benefitted . We have to convience the organization by saying the types of audience , age of audience ,in what way they will be profitted. \nA grand & elegant event will be remembered by people through ages , to afford that , we need some sponsors and even we can use their popularity to our events to reach out ..\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "From Company B , Because people will get effective inspiration by their success stories  from a common man to successful person . \npeople try to find a way to tackle the difficulties  which they face & it helps for them to get hint for the solution from their stories"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608448335664
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608440753427
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608446831807
      }
    ],
    "username": "mothishwaran.c2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 8124137576,
    "first_name": "MOTHISHWARAN",
    "last_name": "C",
    "registration": "19MID0017"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445376030
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the primary function of a critique of your design? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            To improve the overall design. "
          },
          {
            "question": "RGB is to ppi as CMYK is to _.\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Dots per inch "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "blendor,affinity publisher"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "png -lossless\njpg -lossy"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the use of pen tab in illustrator?\n ",
            "answer": "used to draw\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "State types of brushes in brush tool in illustrator. ",
            "answer": "scatter,pattern, art,bristle,calligraphic"
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "option available to merge layer inpanel menu\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "learn to be creative, im at initial state"
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "deadlines makes me to do the work\n"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608446095188
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "yes, hcsr04"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "resistance with rheostat"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "to close electrical circuit and for common logic "
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "red wire to vin\nblack wire to ground\ngreen wire to tx of wifi module\nyellow wire to rx wifi module and controller"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "tx and rx need to free"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "gravity,depth, barometer, proximity,fingerprint,gyrometer"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447211252
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "using social medias,\nadds in tv\nyoutube"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "i will make to feel that working with me is enjoyfull"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "allow them to play games"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447478054
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608444172337
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608445408765
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608446110267
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608447287389
      }
    ],
    "username": "karthick.j2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 8,
    "contact_number": 8667263927,
    "first_name": "Karthick",
    "last_name": "Jayaprakash",
    "registration": "19MIC0118"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be stored in list1 and list2 if the following code is executed?\nList1=[‘a’,’b’,’c’]\nList1+=’de’\nList2=[1,2,3,4]\nList2+=10 ",
            "answer": "\n                                            [‘a’,’b’,’c’,’d’,’e’],error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608470828218
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608469625320
      }
    ],
    "username": "anusha.seshadri2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8921175004,
    "first_name": "Anusha",
    "last_name": "Seshadri",
    "registration": "20BCI0209"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "A prime lens ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Has a fixed focal length "
          },
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": "The vertical movement of a camera on its axis is called ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tilt "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the most difficult part of being a photographer for you? ",
            "answer": "Gauging the correct parameters required to obtain a clear shot quickly before the moment passes"
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the advantage of having a full frame sensor over a crop sensor? ",
            "answer": "Works better than a crop sensor in high ISO"
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "ND filter"
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "Faster aperture will result in a shallower depth of speed."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608441915801
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "A private function can call a protected variable within the same class as long as the variable has been defined in or inherited into the class"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608457210874
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608441303344
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608441939508
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608456008674
      }
    ],
    "username": "kanishk.rath2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 5,
    "contact_number": 9600119330,
    "first_name": "Kanishk",
    "last_name": "Rath",
    "registration": "20BCE0669"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "using thin wires"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Motion Detector\nInfrared Sensors\nfingerprint sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608444441144
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "recursion means calling a function within a function."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445627172
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608444026741
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608444451137
      }
    ],
    "username": "maulik.kansal2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9999047350,
    "first_name": "Maulik",
    "last_name": "Kansal",
    "registration": "20BEE0040"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445121529
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What shutter speed would you use to take a panning shot? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1/30 "
          },
          {
            "question": "A prime lens ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Has a fixed focal length "
          },
          {
            "question": "What does the “bulb” mode in the camera do? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Keeps the shutter open indefinitely "
          },
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the most difficult part of being a photographer for you? ",
            "answer": "From a technical perspective, I hate that the batteries run out so fast in most cameras, and extra batteries are a pain to carry in your pocket. And from a non-tech perspective... I hate that people ask you to take a photo of them, and you have to wait for them to pose, and all, that is super annoying..."
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the advantage of having a full frame sensor over a crop sensor? ",
            "answer": "You get a wider FOV with a full frame sensor, and more exposure as well"
          },
          {
            "question": " What is your favourite lens and why do you prefer it? ",
            "answer": "I like the 55-180mm canon lens, cuz you don't need to go to a really low, F level to get a high enough aperture"
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "Tripod stand"
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "More the curvature of the lens (aperture), the depth perception is more visible, i.e. there is a blur effect as we go farther from the focus point"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445558194
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recursion is when one function is called inside another.... It is mostly used in places where you want to keep creating nested for loops till a condition is satisfied without having to type that number of for loops."
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "yes, it can, only instances of the class can't call protected variables."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608446445316
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608444519998
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608445132729
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608445567049
      }
    ],
    "username": "deepesh.padala2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 7010189621,
    "first_name": "Deepesh ",
    "last_name": "Padala",
    "registration": "20BEC0264"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "It usually refers to calling the function itself again and again , till the time its base condition is satisfied."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608469537170
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the primary function of a critique of your design? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            To improve the overall design. "
          },
          {
            "question": "RGB is to ppi as CMYK is to _.\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Dots per inch "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "No Sir, but excited to Learn New things."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "PNG is of Higher Quality , and JPG is somewhat of Lower Quality."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the use of pen tab in illustrator?\n ",
            "answer": "No Knowledge about it Sir."
          },
          {
            "question": "State types of brushes in brush tool in illustrator. ",
            "answer": "Dont Know Sir."
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "No Answer Sir."
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "As of now , i would not be able to make a project urgently as i have no prior knowledge regarding it."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "The Thought of Future Outcomes of my Works will motivate me."
          },
          {
            "question": "Attach any of your previous work (at least 1) in the attachment below. (can be Event\nposters, Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video Editing, etc.) [ADD A DRIVE LINK] ",
            "answer": "NA"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608478414144
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608468348437
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608477925377
      }
    ],
    "username": "om.dhapodkar2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9755382002,
    "first_name": "Om",
    "last_name": "Dhapodkar",
    "registration": "20BCT0142"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608457831391
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "bla 1"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "bla 2"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "bla 3"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "bla 5"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "bla 7"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "bla 9"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "bla 11"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608457872188
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608457795092
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608457847357
      }
    ],
    "username": "rohan.mittal2018@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 13,
    "contact_number": 8754583601,
    "first_name": "Rohan",
    "last_name": "Mittal",
    "registration": "18BCE0503"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recursion is like a loop but makes even the most complex tasks simple. It loops the function itself un"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "a variable cannot be called, it can be used. However, a protected function can be called by the class members or the members of the subclass(inheriting the base class)"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447939930
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608446736447
      }
    ],
    "username": "aakar.gupta2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9437392551,
    "first_name": "Aakar ",
    "last_name": "Gupta",
    "registration": "19BCE0379"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "I would rate my writing skills at 6. I feel writing, there is always a scope of improvement. I need more practice, support, and teamwork through which I can keep on learning and improving. I love to write and hence will take my work with responsibility. I want to improve my grammar, vocabulary, and style of writing."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "Through writing, I am able to express my thoughts and feelings. It is an important activity to get involved in. Writing also helps one in introspection. I also dream of writing and publishing a book of my own in the future. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "Self-Driving Cars are cars that do not require any human help to drive from one point to another. Programming is used to receive data from the environment, routes, roads, signs, and other vehicles to ensure that there are better traffic controls, increased passenger safety, and streamlined journey. They are a technological breakthrough for mankind. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "Welcome back folks to another mind-blowing event on Machine Learning on 28th December organized by the leading technical club of VIT. IETE-ISF brings you the opportunity to dwell in the world of Machine learning and explore your interests in it. So much to learn, So less time. What are you waiting for? Register below :"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I visited  Emirates Mall with my family for Ice-Skiing and there they asked me a question about global warming which I answered correctly. So they allowed me to take a personal picture with a real penguin."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "I always write down all the events, works, assignments and other stuff that I need to get completed in a day or in a week. I give priority to those assignments that have their deadlines closer. I also use sticky notes to remember my tasks. "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "My passion to write and contribute to a club that would uplift me and would give me some life-cherishing memories motivated me to apply for IETE's editorial team."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445849450
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I will approach the respective student and ask for his/her needs and understand their problem. I ( or maybe even our team) will look for possible solutions to his/her problem. I may suggest them to take a break from club activities and rejoin with a refreshed mind."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "First of all, I will discuss with the other event's coordinator whether they plan to postpone their event. I would convince their team that our event is a really big one with many important guests in it. If no positive result takes place9which should be highly unlikely), I would try to look for other venues where our event can take place smoothly.\nTo prevent something like this in the future, I(along with my team) would be fully prepared with our event planning in a day or two in advance and notify the same to Clubs & Chapters Committee.  "
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "If possible we would arrange for more seats, chairs, etc. If not, we'll email the leftover registrations about the issue and kindly apologize for the same. We could even email the recording of the event to everyone who couldn't attend the event."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would firstly require sample speakers from company B at least a week before the event to test the sound quality and technical glitches (if any) in them with our team. If their speaker meets our expectations and charges lesser money than company A, we can tie up with B for our future events."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "We can add their product/service on our social media handle or add in our social media posts either in the design or caption. We can also mention and thank them at various intervals of the event."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "So would first analyze the time I will require for both the works. Accordingly, I will set the time limit for each of them with some flexibility. It also depends on my preparation with the subject and the importance of the paper for academics."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "First of all, our team will be prepared to handle such an emergency. We will pick the best speaker from our club to take the original speaker's place and explain to the crowd about the abrupt change of speakers. We "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447377780
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608444075305
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608445874075
      }
    ],
    "username": "devansh.mudgal2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9179379134,
    "first_name": "Devansh",
    "last_name": "Mudgal",
    "registration": "20BCB0113"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608445751741
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608445563432
      }
    ],
    "username": "adhiraj.saxena2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8827117111,
    "first_name": "Adhiraj",
    "last_name": "Saxena",
    "registration": "20BEC0298"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445711274
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608444507505
      }
    ],
    "username": "adamnellissery.jijo2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 918138802776,
    "first_name": "Adam",
    "last_name": "Jijo",
    "registration": "20BCI0077"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true for microcontrollers and microprocessors? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both contain processing unit "
          },
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "using an inductor and ac current\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "gyroscope, compass, proximity sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445225198
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608444022424
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608445246059
      }
    ],
    "username": "diptanshu.de2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 9748136665,
    "first_name": "Diptanshu",
    "last_name": "De",
    "registration": "20BEE0016"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445273518
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608444069114
      }
    ],
    "username": "aryan.shekhar2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8800504809,
    "first_name": "Aryan",
    "last_name": "Shekhar",
    "registration": "20BCE0645"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true for microcontrollers and microprocessors? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both contain processing unit "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "HCSR04 ultrasonic sensor"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "increasing the wire length.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "providing a common logical reference level for the circuit."
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "ESP8266 Wifi module."
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "reset pin\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "proximity sensor\ngyroscope\nfingerprint sensor\n"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445240392
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608444036908
      }
    ],
    "username": "sebin.puthiyath2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9447103196,
    "first_name": "SEBIN",
    "last_name": "PUTHIYATH",
    "registration": "20MVD0047"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "7.5,I would rate my self an average writer and I have to improve my vocabulary."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "writing is a better way to express our thoughts"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "self driving cars are one the best developments of 21st century. Self driving cars are already sold by Tesla and it helps very much in long distance travelling. There are still a lot of work to be done like adding infrastructure to support the innovation. They can avoid accidents occurring to drinking and driving which is one of the major causes to accidents."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "'\"Artificial Intelligence\" the \".com\" killer"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I think for me there's much to accomplish in upcoming days, as of now I don't think I've accomplished anything that I am very proud of there's a lot to learn for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "I set my short term time table for work which has to be completed in specific time.  "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "Clubs are perfect place to get exposure, I am interested in electronics and I need to improve in Programming and technical areas so I feel editorial team would be right for me."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445336362
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "7.5,I would rate my self an average writer and I have to improve my vocabulary."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "writing is a better way to express our thoughts"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "self driving cars are one the best developments of 21st century. Self driving cars are already sold by Tesla and it helps very much in long distance travelling. There are still a lot of work to be done like adding infrastructure to support the innovation. They can avoid accidents occurring to drinking and driving which is one of the major causes to accidents."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "'\"Artificial Intelligence\" the \".com\" killer"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I think for me there's much to accomplish in upcoming days, as of now I don't think I've accomplished anything that I am very proud of there's a lot to learn for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "I set my short term time table for work which has to be completed in specific time.  "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "Clubs are perfect place to get exposure, I am interested in electronics and I need to improve in Programming and technical areas so I feel editorial team would be right for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "7.5,I would rate my self an average writer and I have to improve my vocabulary."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "writing is a better way to express our thoughts"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "self driving cars are one the best developments of 21st century. Self driving cars are already sold by Tesla and it helps very much in long distance travelling. There are still a lot of work to be done like adding infrastructure to support the innovation. They can avoid accidents occurring to drinking and driving which is one of the major causes to accidents."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "'\"Artificial Intelligence\" the \".com\" killer"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I think for me there's much to accomplish in upcoming days, as of now I don't think I've accomplished anything that I am very proud of there's a lot to learn for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "I set my short term time table for work which has to be completed in specific time.  "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "Clubs are perfect place to get exposure, I am interested in electronics and I need to improve in Programming and technical areas so I feel editorial team would be right for me."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445336605
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "7.5,I would rate my self an average writer and I have to improve my vocabulary."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "writing is a better way to express our thoughts"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "self driving cars are one the best developments of 21st century. Self driving cars are already sold by Tesla and it helps very much in long distance travelling. There are still a lot of work to be done like adding infrastructure to support the innovation. They can avoid accidents occurring to drinking and driving which is one of the major causes to accidents."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "'\"Artificial Intelligence\" the \".com\" killer"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I think for me there's much to accomplish in upcoming days, as of now I don't think I've accomplished anything that I am very proud of there's a lot to learn for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "I set my short term time table for work which has to be completed in specific time.  "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "Clubs are perfect place to get exposure, I am interested in electronics and I need to improve in Programming and technical areas so I feel editorial team would be right for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "7.5,I would rate my self an average writer and I have to improve my vocabulary."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "writing is a better way to express our thoughts"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "self driving cars are one the best developments of 21st century. Self driving cars are already sold by Tesla and it helps very much in long distance travelling. There are still a lot of work to be done like adding infrastructure to support the innovation. They can avoid accidents occurring to drinking and driving which is one of the major causes to accidents."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "'\"Artificial Intelligence\" the \".com\" killer"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I think for me there's much to accomplish in upcoming days, as of now I don't think I've accomplished anything that I am very proud of there's a lot to learn for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "I set my short term time table for work which has to be completed in specific time.  "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "Clubs are perfect place to get exposure, I am interested in electronics and I need to improve in Programming and technical areas so I feel editorial team would be right for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "7.5,I would rate my self an average writer and I have to improve my vocabulary."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "writing is a better way to express our thoughts"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "self driving cars are one the best developments of 21st century. Self driving cars are already sold by Tesla and it helps very much in long distance travelling. There are still a lot of work to be done like adding infrastructure to support the innovation. They can avoid accidents occurring to drinking and driving which is one of the major causes to accidents."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "'\"Artificial Intelligence\" the \".com\" killer"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I think for me there's much to accomplish in upcoming days, as of now I don't think I've accomplished anything that I am very proud of there's a lot to learn for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "I set my short term time table for work which has to be completed in specific time.  "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "Clubs are perfect place to get exposure, I am interested in electronics and I need to improve in Programming and technical areas so I feel editorial team would be right for me."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445337050
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "7.5,I would rate my self an average writer and I have to improve my vocabulary."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "writing is a better way to express our thoughts"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "self driving cars are one the best developments of 21st century. Self driving cars are already sold by Tesla and it helps very much in long distance travelling. There are still a lot of work to be done like adding infrastructure to support the innovation. They can avoid accidents occurring to drinking and driving which is one of the major causes to accidents."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "'\"Artificial Intelligence\" the \".com\" killer"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I think for me there's much to accomplish in upcoming days, as of now I don't think I've accomplished anything that I am very proud of there's a lot to learn for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "I set my short term time table for work which has to be completed in specific time.  "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "Clubs are perfect place to get exposure, I am interested in electronics and I need to improve in Programming and technical areas so I feel editorial team would be right for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "7.5,I would rate my self an average writer and I have to improve my vocabulary."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "writing is a better way to express our thoughts"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "self driving cars are one the best developments of 21st century. Self driving cars are already sold by Tesla and it helps very much in long distance travelling. There are still a lot of work to be done like adding infrastructure to support the innovation. They can avoid accidents occurring to drinking and driving which is one of the major causes to accidents."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "'\"Artificial Intelligence\" the \".com\" killer"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I think for me there's much to accomplish in upcoming days, as of now I don't think I've accomplished anything that I am very proud of there's a lot to learn for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "I set my short term time table for work which has to be completed in specific time.  "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "Clubs are perfect place to get exposure, I am interested in electronics and I need to improve in Programming and technical areas so I feel editorial team would be right for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "7.5,I would rate my self an average writer and I have to improve my vocabulary."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "writing is a better way to express our thoughts"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "self driving cars are one the best developments of 21st century. Self driving cars are already sold by Tesla and it helps very much in long distance travelling. There are still a lot of work to be done like adding infrastructure to support the innovation. They can avoid accidents occurring to drinking and driving which is one of the major causes to accidents."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "'\"Artificial Intelligence\" the \".com\" killer"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I think for me there's much to accomplish in upcoming days, as of now I don't think I've accomplished anything that I am very proud of there's a lot to learn for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "I set my short term time table for work which has to be completed in specific time.  "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "Clubs are perfect place to get exposure, I am interested in electronics and I need to improve in Programming and technical areas so I feel editorial team would be right for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "7.5,I would rate my self an average writer and I have to improve my vocabulary."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "writing is a better way to express our thoughts"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "self driving cars are one the best developments of 21st century. Self driving cars are already sold by Tesla and it helps very much in long distance travelling. There are still a lot of work to be done like adding infrastructure to support the innovation. They can avoid accidents occurring to drinking and driving which is one of the major causes to accidents."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "'\"Artificial Intelligence\" the \".com\" killer"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I think for me there's much to accomplish in upcoming days, as of now I don't think I've accomplished anything that I am very proud of there's a lot to learn for me."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "I set my short term time table for work which has to be completed in specific time.  "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "Clubs are perfect place to get exposure, I am interested in electronics and I need to improve in Programming and technical areas so I feel editorial team would be right for me."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445344513
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "social media is the place to publicize any events. People are on their phone for the entire time and instagram would be the place to advertise."
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "It would be uncomfortable to know if a team doesn't want to work with me. I am open to have a conversation if there was a mistake from my side and try to solve the problem if possible."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "It is important to make sure that there shouldn't be any confusion in the venue. we should check in to the venue in person and confirm the booking. If there occurs such a problem and if the events have things in common then we can have a conversation with organizer of the other event to know if there's a chance to combine the events."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "If the registrations exceed the capacity we should politely apologize to the participants and make sure that they know that it's not possible to exceed the capacity of venue. We must inform them about any event happening in future or conducted at the time any of the other clubs in the college."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for an event as they act as advertising for the event. Sponsors show that the event is not just a scam. The sponsors and the organizers should have mutual respect and maintain professionalism"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "speaker from B would be preferable because that would help both the start up and the participants because their ideas helped their rapid growth and participants can hear to their ideas and how to become successful"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "It might be necessary to organize an event in a unique way because that draws attention of the students."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608446825828
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true for microcontrollers and microprocessors? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both contain processing unit "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447180780
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608444172985
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608445364487
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608446839720
      }
    ],
    "username": "bharath.v2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 9,
    "contact_number": 9741303504,
    "first_name": "Bharath",
    "last_name": "V",
    "registration": "20BEC0716"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "Some of the main advertising techniques are as follows\n1. Online marketing campaings involving relevant content and engagement from the viewers.  \n2. Developing hashtags to increase engagement \n3.Call to action prompts to all social media posts is essential "
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "Team work is essential for any event to be a success . Disunity and conflict within  a group can cause the event to fall apart. Incase a team member does not want to work with me I would try to sit down with that individual and find out that deeprooted reason and try to win that team memebe over."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "We will have to arrange for more seating capacity , however if we have over shot our capacity we will have to conduct a second event. Therefore a little extra space while booking is always importants"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsorship is one of the most important and powerful marketing tools. They attract more people to the event and can persuade customers to make purchases or take part in the event\n The key factors are\n1. Brand Awareness : \n2. Sales and Revenues of that company\n3. How different are they from the competitors\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would get a speaker from company B as it would be a new face for an event and can target a niche audience for a particular event. \nIt helps to reach a newer market and opens up avenues to better branding strategies ."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": " Being creative is an important factor while coming up with a campain as it helps to attract a greater audience . A standard procedure would not be able to optimize creativity and will not generate high footfall as a unique idea would. "
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "I study regularly and manage my time effectively hence I wont have to put in too much time other than revision  and can hence do justice to any work given to me."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": " I will make sure that there would be a backup speaker for the event given any unforeseen circumstances arise"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I would attend the meeting which was informed to me first and would talk to the the other club heads regarding the clash of the timings and would take a briefing from there or some of my core members."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "I would find a middle path and highlight the pro cons of why i feel it is necessary"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445922329
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608444419982
      }
    ],
    "username": "karthik.mehrotra2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8390787238,
    "first_name": "Karthik",
    "last_name": "Mehrotra",
    "registration": "20BEC0691"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "Yes"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608450956530
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "A prime lens ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Has a fixed focal length "
          },
          {
            "question": "What does the “bulb” mode in the camera do? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Keeps the shutter open indefinitely "
          },
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": "The vertical movement of a camera on its axis is called ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tilt "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the most difficult part of being a photographer for you? ",
            "answer": "Carrying and taking good care of the equipments without them being damaged is very important. We should be alert at all times wait with patience to click the right picture."
          },
          {
            "question": " What is your favourite lens and why do you prefer it? ",
            "answer": "I like macro lenses as I'm more into macro photography and nature photography."
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "Camera, tripod, ND filters"
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "The wider the aperture, shallower is the depth of field and smaller the aperture, deeper is the depth of field."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608451486425
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "No. No need to import a library to use ultrasonic sensor."
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "Use a potentiometer or heat the  circuit."
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "The GND pins are used to close a circuit"
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "By connecting it to a ESP8266 WiFi module"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "1. IR Sensor\n2. Gyroscope\n3. Fingerprint Sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608452296369
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608449845837
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608450986969
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608451499679
      }
    ],
    "username": "dhruvakrishnama.rajua2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 9842902490,
    "first_name": "A Dhruva",
    "last_name": "Krishnama Raju ",
    "registration": "20BCE0907"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "calling of a function repetedly"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445308687
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608444115696
      }
    ],
    "username": "shaurya.sharma2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9560119550,
    "first_name": "Shaurya",
    "last_name": "Sharma",
    "registration": "20BCE0655"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445550244
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1) Publicizing through Instagram Stories, posts and promotions.\n2) Publicizing through facebook advertisements.\n3) Creating electronic blogs and banners to attract students from respective domains. "
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I will try to understand what problem he/she has. I will definitely convince him/her and try to help the person so that he/she again gains the interest to work in the team."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "I will try to convey to the other parties that the auditorium was prebooked by me for our event and there was some confusion due to which the other party didn't get to know about that. I will tell them about the importance of our event and also tell that many important people are coming there and it can't be postponed.\nNext time, I will keep a regular track about the venue of the event and will not stop inquiring until and unless the event successfully takes place."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I will ask the manager of the venue to get some extra space for some more people. I will tell him to place the chairs closely so that more space can be gained for the extra set of people."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are an easy way for money. They get their advertisement and we get the money for showcasing them in our events. Also the events look much more professional when someone is sponsoring them.\nI would see that whether the company or organisation that I am approaching for the sponsorship is reputated or not. I will also check that whether those guys have a clean history free of frauds and all or not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to get the speakers from the both the companies. Company A is well established so that would create a very greater and professional impact on the audience of my event and Company B is although new but I would just want to promote them by inviting a speaker from their company."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "It's not necessary to come up with an unique idea to organize an event. It just depends on personal perspective, but I would definitely like to do something unique to gain audience's attraction."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "1) We can advertise on social media platforms like Facebook, Instagram,etc as now - a - days almost everyone uses them.\n2) We can make attractive and mesmerizing e-posters to promote our products.\n3) We can use SEO (Search Engine Optimization) to know about people's choices and then advertise the particular."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "I will not prioritize any specific  one. I will try to give time to both of them. I am a person who revise stuff form exams regularly so I do not have to mug up things one day before the exam. I just need revision which does not take much time. So, I ca divide my time for both of them."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will tell everyone the truth. I will tell them that the speaker had got some serious medical issues and will tell them to understand the situation. I will tell them that the event will start without the speaker's speech and they need not to worry."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I will choose the one in which I am required the most. As the other one, I can just ask my friend of that club that what was discussed and what work do I have to actually do."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "I will carry out a diplomatic approach. I will do something which is neither in my will nor in their's, but would be good for the workshop for sure."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447081091
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608444389269
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608445576748
      }
    ],
    "username": "kartikeya.rawat2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 7906992014,
    "first_name": "Kartikeya",
    "last_name": "Rawat",
    "registration": "20BCE0641"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "No , as there are many whatsapp groups created for the freshers to publisise the event and we can also tag vit vellore on our instagram to promote the event on official website "
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I will talk to my team leader and ask him to take a meeting to motivate the other member to motivate them to indulge in more club activities "
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "we will talk to that event coordinator to do the even"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "we will plan this from the ideation stage as if the students exceed we will talk to the authority to shift the venue as many students wont adjust to previous venue ."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "sponsors are very important factor for an event as it motivates the participants getting perks and cash rewards while working with dedication to win the contest . so to approach sponsors ww will send a  MOU to the organization by writing all the advantages why to collaborate with this  club events and our expected students to participate and saw your organization logo and  to be a part of  your organization product and services after the event ."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "as we will take well established company as most students want to listen to the speakers who are from a reputed organization for big events like hackathons but for regular events  we can call some speakers from start ups companies as they can able to guide students during there semester exams what to do from scratch "
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "creative idea stimulates the audience to know more about the event identity as they  want to be a part of the event . by brainstorming a creative events helps students to go for that ."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "event posters , club instagram handles , promoting product and services during the event ."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "i always follow time management so i can choose one slot time to do that work on that interval of time"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "we can keep two speakers for that event as if one is not able to arrive 2nd one can handle the situation "
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "by choosing the important one listen to that club meeting and keep another tab on to other and after that cjeck their MOM after the club meeting of that club which i didnt find important ."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "we can divide our work of what we getting from the team leader .as  the other can know what he wants to do in that workshop so that a proper coordination will be there "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608446324256
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608444807996
      }
    ],
    "username": "rahul.jindal2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 6263316161,
    "first_name": "Rahul ",
    "last_name": "Jindal",
    "registration": "19BBA0013"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445852691
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608444649045
      }
    ],
    "username": "preksha.mathur2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9599225419,
    "first_name": "Preksha",
    "last_name": "Mathur",
    "registration": "20BCE2203"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be stored in list1 and list2 if the following code is executed?\nList1=[‘a’,’b’,’c’]\nList1+=’de’\nList2=[1,2,3,4]\nList2+=10 ",
            "answer": "\n                                            [‘a’,’b’,’c’,’d’,’e’],error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608445940806
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608444737457
      }
    ],
    "username": "akhilsrinivas.p2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7904162451,
    "first_name": "Akhil",
    "last_name": "Srinivas P",
    "registration": "20BCE0567"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608446393621
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608445210657
      }
    ],
    "username": "niravra.baksi2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9382975770,
    "first_name": "Niravra",
    "last_name": "Baksi",
    "registration": "20BCI0153"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recursion means defining a problem in terms of itself. It is like calling a function in its own definition code structure. Functions calls itself directly or indirectly."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608446809580
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608445587546
      }
    ],
    "username": "gagan.parashar2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9119375927,
    "first_name": "Gagan",
    "last_name": "Parashar",
    "registration": "20BKT0075"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608446843845
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Try contacting admin of student's social media grps and spread messages in them.\n2. Making students interact with board members so that they can get insight of club.\n3. Approach students through social media domains and show them past achievements of the club."
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I would first discuss the problem calmly and try to find a feasible solution. If this does not work i would fix different time slots for us to work so as to not face each other and not hamper productivity of the team. "
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "If such situation happens first i will try to talk to other event head and try to come to a possible midway by dividing time slots or requesting them to postpone their event if possible. If it does not work then i will try to find some other place by the money compensated by auditorium. To avoid these kind of situations i would before hand ask for a conformation reciept and personally talk to manager of auditorium to check for any such possibilities. "
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "In such a case i would request younger audience to enjoy the function by leaving their seats and would plan some activity for them while seats which are vacant now can be given to others."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are very crucial for an event because good event requires good monetary funding as well for customer satisfaction. Key factors which i will look for are that the company is supporting towards creative minds, next is that they do not promote something that is hazardous or socially unacceptable, also they keep faith in organizers."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "A speaker from company A will be preffered since they have much more experience since they have experienced phase of company B already and they are the one which can provide a better perspective "
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "A unique idea is always a better approach since it can attract young minds and also different things attract much."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "the best way to publicize is by targetting a specific audience and tempting them by some posters or a skit for offline mode. for online mode video is good."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "i would divide time slots but complete work for both sides surely"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "i will first inform the audience then later arrange for some speaker who can arrive in lesser time to not let people fell being cheated."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "i would consider which meeting is more important at that time, which club requires me more at that instant and then take decision accordingly"
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "i would try my best to convince other member but if it does not work i will try to find a mid way failing to which i will agree on their terms."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608448368549
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608445620195
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608446880973
      }
    ],
    "username": "nikkhil.chopra2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9828993888,
    "first_name": "Nikkhil",
    "last_name": "Chopra",
    "registration": "20BCE0927"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recusion is a process of calling out the same function again in the function code only to get result and avoid lengthy codes.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "No a private function can;t "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608449460360
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608448257234
      }
    ],
    "username": "pratham.agrawal2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8269067007,
    "first_name": "Pratham",
    "last_name": "Agrawal",
    "registration": "20BDS0142"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be stored in list1 and list2 if the following code is executed?\nList1=[‘a’,’b’,’c’]\nList1+=’de’\nList2=[1,2,3,4]\nList2+=10 ",
            "answer": "\n                                            [‘a’,’b’,’c’,’d’,’e’],error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "It is the function that calls itself during its execution "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447142180
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the primary function of a critique of your design? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            To improve the overall design. "
          },
          {
            "question": "RGB is to ppi as CMYK is to _.\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Dots per inch "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "For video editing I use flimora and inshot. For graphic designing and photo editing I use photoshop and PicsArt. For drawing I have sketch book in my Ipad"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "Jpg can be compressed with some loss of data but png can be compressed without  loss of data and do not reduce the quality of the image. Jpg is for normal image storing but png is for photo editing and artworks."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the use of pen tab in illustrator?\n ",
            "answer": "The pen tab is used to draw the diagrams. It is also used to reshape and edit."
          },
          {
            "question": "State types of brushes in brush tool in illustrator. ",
            "answer": "Art brush, pattern brush, smudge brush."
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "By clicking the merge layers in the layer box. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "I have a interest in doing creative things and exploring them. I will use some parts of my previous design. I will save the best part of my design for the future use."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "I look my previous designs and some extraordinary designs of others . So that I can get motivation and an idea to accomplish the task.  I will take up interesting and challenging one . So I can make the mood to work."
          },
          {
            "question": "Attach any of your previous work (at least 1) in the attachment below. (can be Event\nposters, Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video Editing, etc.) [ADD A DRIVE LINK] ",
            "answer": "https://drive.google.com/folderview?id=10UYNh0DYf5dCtRVJ_BF5onQVNsRptg6o\n"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608448965753
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "May be 8"
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "My thoughts that i have"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "One of the great technological advancements in 21st century is the mobile. We have world in our hands. Now we do everything by sitting comfortably in a room. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "Learn to teach your Machines using MACHINE LEARNING @ 28 th December using google meet "
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "My proud accomplishment is when I get centum in science and social in my 10th boards. I was the one to score 100 in my school. I think I got return for my hard works. I get motivation from that whenever I feel low."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "Write what ever Comes to my mind in a paper. And I arrange them in the perfect order and mention the time and the duration.\nLike, \nTask -1\n  Sub task -1\n  ....\n  .\nTask - 2\n  Sub task -1\n  ...\n  .\n  .\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "My creativity, curiosity to learn new things and correct my mistakes."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608450127250
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608445938577
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608447162332
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608448982265
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608450154117
      }
    ],
    "username": "sadhana.2020b@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 7,
    "contact_number": 6380339856,
    "first_name": "Sadhana ",
    "last_name": "S",
    "registration": "20MIS0185"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "recursion is calling of a function by inside a function it may be called inside a same function then it is referred as direct recursion it may be called by a diff function then it may be referred as indirect recursion"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "yes"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447198220
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608446074256
      }
    ],
    "username": "anupam.sudhakaran2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8006944707,
    "first_name": "Anupam",
    "last_name": "Sudhakaran",
    "registration": "20BCI0133"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608479912490
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1.Different seminars should be organized by the club members to make the freshers know more about their club, the can send out their representative in different freshers group  so the club also look more approachable.\n\n2.Creating their   own platform wherein the send out their  openings and the information about the club, about the recruitment process, this should be like website as if a freshers apply in many different clubs his/her WhatsApp gets spammed by different club's messages.\n\n3.Sharing behind the scenes videos of how things operate in the club , how management people assign task to different people, how  technical people   work for the club."
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I would motivate and inspire him to work towards clubs goal  and vision."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "So I would  initially request the auditorium  people to provide us with the hall, if that doesn't  happen I would make arrangement to organize the same in a open theater .\n\nThe steps I would take beforehand are:\n1.Book  some other hall as well to be secured enough.\n2.If the location changes, be ready with WhatsApp messages for the change in location of the seminar and be ready to deploy them fast.\n3.Also double check the booking for no last minute confusions."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I would conduct the event in two shift morning and evening."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would invite the person from company B because :\n1.As he is a part of a new start-up he could guide students well about what is new in the start-up industry  and what are the challenges faced in the current times, this is what the established ones will lack .\n\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I think it is necessary to come up with unique or creative ideas as it is the impression  and the kind of image we develop, people remember."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608481362239
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608478708976
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608479922273
      }
    ],
    "username": "harshvardhan.agarwal2020a@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9752433699,
    "first_name": "Harshvardhan",
    "last_name": "Agarwal",
    "registration": "20MIC0157"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608447617200
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "the servo library"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "resistance also depends upon temperature length and thickness.\nso longer wires, thinner wires and higher temperature of wires will increase the resistance of the wire"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "to avoid excess current going into the arduino board."
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "we can use the esp8266wifi module and that can give access to wifi to the arduino microcontroller. This module has an integrated tcp/ip stack."
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "the tx and rx pins."
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "proximity sensor, ambient light sensor and fingerprint sensor."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608448830363
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608446036833
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608447697538
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608447774918
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608448844482
      }
    ],
    "username": "shakthimahendran.b2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 9108219850,
    "first_name": "Shakthi ",
    "last_name": "Mahendran",
    "registration": "19BEC0520"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true for microcontrollers and microprocessors? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both contain processing unit "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "by decreasing the current "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "It is ground pins used to connect the negative terminals."
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "By using a wifi board."
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "proximity sensor, accelerometer, touch sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447242917
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608446195997
      }
    ],
    "username": "johny.john2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9188107835,
    "first_name": "Johny",
    "last_name": "John",
    "registration": "20BEE0028"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "CALLING A FUNCTION AFTER GETTING INSIDE THE SAME FUNCTION"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "NO"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608452322345
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "-approaching them via mails\n-asking club members to promote the club on various platforms \n-by showing projects done by club members(most attractive)"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "try to negotiate about the reason for not working together \nthe only reason which can be suitable \ninvolving someone else can't solve that i think"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "there might be no issues if the previous event ends before \nsecondly, we can discuss with the other team if they can arrange somewhere else, or can we get any other hall or something in the same venue"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "we can arrange some other hall and telecast the event there,\nor \nwe can simply reject the exceeded registrations in case of no arrangement "
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "that's all about money for the event\napproach- \nthe sponsor should have any kind of relationship with the event happening \nlike some tech industry is sponsoring for an event of coding, or why coding is important"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "inviting speaker depends on our audience\nif our audience is new learners we should invite from B\nif our audience is kind of with sufficient knowledge about the event we can call from A "
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "yes unique and creative ideas are neccesary "
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "depending on the product both online and offline can be better"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "if i am  playing a great role in that urgent work i will priorities that\notherwise paper"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608453448160
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608451144152
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608452368667
      }
    ],
    "username": "jasshu.garg2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 8195850098,
    "first_name": "Jasshu",
    "last_name": "garg",
    "registration": "19BCT0082"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What shutter speed would you use to take a panning shot? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1/30 "
          },
          {
            "question": "A prime lens ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Has a fixed focal length "
          },
          {
            "question": "What does the “bulb” mode in the camera do? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Keeps the shutter open indefinitely "
          },
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": "The vertical movement of a camera on its axis is called ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tilt "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the most difficult part of being a photographer for you? ",
            "answer": "The first thing is to take difficult shots in a dim atmosphere during dark. Also, visualization of a form or creation is sometimes difficult, the next is to implement the ideas we have."
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the advantage of having a full frame sensor over a crop sensor? ",
            "answer": "full frame sensors can provide a broader dynamic range and has a good low light performance so the quality is better."
          },
          {
            "question": " What is your favourite lens and why do you prefer it? ",
            "answer": "my favorite one is Nikon 70-200 mm. It allows to take numerous shots as it is super fast, performance is vey good and picture becomes very sharp and clear."
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "An ND filter is the thing to use in such situation as it will cut specific amount of light and that makes it best for brighter conditions Best ones are 6 stop and 10 stop."
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "There is an inverse proportion between them. Smaller the aperture size, greater is the depth of field and vice-versa. "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447441148
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608446444239
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608446625419
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608446681519
      }
    ],
    "username": "adamya.2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 7292828255,
    "first_name": "Adamya",
    "last_name": "S",
    "registration": "19BCE0518"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recursion is the calling of a function by its own and its repetition of the same function by itself until a certain condition is met."
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "Yes it can be called if the private function is a child function or a friend function."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447472587
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1-By advertising in social media platforms.\n2-By holding some workshops online through various softwares.\n3-By holding quizzes with interesting prizes."
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I would talk to him as to why is he having a problem and would try to work out a compromise so that we can work together in the future."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "If a thing like this happens then I would talk to the second event organiser about his/her event and their timings. I would negotiate with them of doing an event in which both the events could be merged so that both can do the event in the large auditorium without much space congestion. To avoid this I would advertise my event so that there is no confusion beforehand of the place and timings of the event."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "If a thing like this happens then I would prefer to divide the participants in different slots according to the capacity of the venue so that everyone can attend the meeting with comfort."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "In my opinion sponsors are crucial for an event as they give the financial power to the event we organise so that we can reach to a large audience and with them they also bring in a brand reputation due to which the event becomes more recognised and reliable."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would call a person working from company B as that person would know more about the current market situation for up and coming talents and then he can encourage them and motivate them to the right direction."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "It is necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organise an event so that we can evolve more and attract more new people for our event."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "We can publicise a sponsor product by using them ourselves and then talking about its benefit and we can also publicise them by organising special competitions for it or by issuing our special coupons or codes in it for the participants."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "I would prioritise my main work of exams to an extent so that I can get a respectable marks in it and then prioritise the work of my chapter's urgent work."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "If a situation like this happens then I would see if I have any contact of an alternate speaker with me otherwise I would handle the situation with an alternate lecture in which my team is good at."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I would attend the meeting of the chapter of whose work I am more enthusiastic about and ask my friend in the other chapters for some notes of the meeting in the other ones."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "I would talk to the other person and come to a compromise on that points."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608449093509
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608446344167
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608447610402
      }
    ],
    "username": "akshat.bisht2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 8006565650,
    "first_name": "Akshat",
    "last_name": "Bisht",
    "registration": "20BCE0629"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recursion is a process in which a function calls itself again and again till the base case is encountered."
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "No."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608450059545
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time  I will the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608451724840
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time  I will the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608451726737
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time  I will the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608451727869
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time  I will the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Use social media, popular social media pages to publicise the club.\n2. Conduct small and interesting competitions on social media with prizes.\n3. Help the students in these times with motivation and study material circulated through social media.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If a team member is not willing to work with me , firstly I will try to find out the reason why. Then if we can talk out any problems among us that would be best. Else if with some of my compromises the team benefits, I will be ready to do so. Else, I will try to find someone else who can do his/her part of the job and is willing to work with me."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1. Firstly, to avoid such situations, I will be keeping in touch with the auditorium authorities, reminding them about our event and telling them to arrange everything nicely. Also, I will keep a backup auditorium in my sight .\n2.In such situation , I will look what was the confusion that led to the situation. I will ask the auditorium authorities to allot us the auditorium as we had booked it first. I will ask the other party to look for auditorium somewhere else as we had booked it first. By the time I am doing all this, I will ask my colleagues to look for somewhere else where we can conduct our program.\nIf nothing happens , I will postpone the program, or will try to conduct it online."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will try to make the program offline cum online, so that the extra ones are accommodated in the online platform. Else, I will try to accommodate them in the same place by adding extra chairs. Else, I will cancel the registration of the extra participants at that time, and arrange another program for them with new registrations, where there will be a cap on registering participants.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for a program as without money, no program can be organised.\nThe key factor will be whether the sponsor has enough resources to sponsor our program and whether the topic of program resonates with sponsor not."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would like to the speaker from company B, because being a part of a growing startup , he will know the difficulties faced to run a company among the top players, he will be able to guide the audience better on how to deal with difficult situation, and how to grow more among the top players starting from raw."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would like to choose a creative idea for an event, as it will be unique, different from others."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "To publicise the sponsors, we can give goodies to the participants with the logo of the sponsors. Using posters of sponsors where the event is conducted. Mentioning them in between the event from time to time."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I will prepare for my paper beforehand throughout the semester , to give time tol the chapter's work. "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask some people from audience to put forward their views and will use internet resources to conduct the program."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608451727944
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608448871712
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608450101193
      }
    ],
    "username": "avinash.singh2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 7,
    "contact_number": 8400725444,
    "first_name": "Avinash",
    "last_name": "Singh",
    "registration": "20BCE0494"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "we can double down on our social media promotions.\nWe can start a youtube channel.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "If it requires us to work together we have no choice but to set aside our differences and swallow our pride to finish the job.\nI will tell him/her to do so.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "I will get in contact with the staff of the auditorium and explain them the gravity of the situation and ask them to assign it to us otherwise I will have to delay the event  and look for backup options.\nGood communication and backups are required to avoid the situation."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I will break it into batches and  extend the time of the event.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "sponsorship is important for the economic point of view as we might not have the funds for smooth functioning of an event.\nfor sponsorship , the organization should believe in our idea and vision."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "we should get company B as it can get us new ideas and attract newer audience. Although we should not cut off our relationship with A."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "I would mix it up a little.\nThe standard protocol is what got us our audience base but we need to give new Ideas a try once in a while to expand it.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "we can wear the merchandise and use the product in our events."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "I would give my best shot to complete both but I would prioritize the chapter's work.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will try to get the speaker back but if that is not  the case I would again look for backup and get a capable speaker from my contacts or I can speak on my own."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I will attend the one that is more important to me and get info about the other from my mates in that club."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": " find a middle ground."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608448185067
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608446679717
      }
    ],
    "username": "deepanshu.sharma2020a@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9820747362,
    "first_name": "DEEPANSHU",
    "last_name": "SHARMA",
    "registration": "20BEE0300"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "is a common mathematical and programming concept.It means that a function calls itself."
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "a protected variable cannot be accessed by users of the class but can be accessed inside a subclass that inherits from the class."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447813463
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608446642765
      }
    ],
    "username": "vansh.mahajan2020a@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8375837671,
    "first_name": "Vansh",
    "last_name": "Mahajan",
    "registration": "20BCI0184"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608448484952
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608447279425
      }
    ],
    "username": "tallam.rahul2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9063507164,
    "first_name": "Tallam",
    "last_name": "Rahul",
    "registration": "20BCI0114"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608447996798
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "People have been watching films, series, and videos since the lockdown has started. Our generation is completely into them. Thus we could make a kind of short film advertising our club in a funny yet efficient way. This would help us to catch the attention of the newcomers and will also make them realize that there is both fun and learning in our club."
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "It's very important to understand the viewpoint of others too. Thus I would first try to find out the reasons, why he/she dislikes me. If I find that it I actually was doing wrong, I would first try to apologize and would work upon myself to improve the shortcomings. Otherwise, I would discuss with the person about the issue and try to explain to him my viewpoint too, such that we get to a final decision and no hard feelings are left. Its important for me to complete the work, thus without wasting further time. I would come up with a plan with my team so that everyone is happy and we are able to complete the task in time."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "So this kind of unforeseen circumstances occurs many times in our life. Its important to understand that every time, everything won't go in our direction. So instead of feeling bad and frustrated and without wasting my further time, I would come up with a plan with my team. My  opinion would have been to book a different auditorium. The size, infrastructure, etc it doesn't matter because the place doesn't matter but the even does so. I would try to find a place on our own campus that meets with all the conditions which are required for the event to take place. I would also compromise with a few things if I have to. To avoid such things in the future, I will always try to keep a backup plan with me. That, if the things I had planned don't go accordingly, I will always have an alternate solution to such things."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "First, if this happens, I will try to find a website or application, which is easy to open and install and has a limit in which all m participants are able to join, I would share the link in several places like the mail, WhatsApp, etc so that every person gets the information. Also having a live event on youtube is a nice solution to such a problem."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are very crucial for an event to take place because without them our event does not have a brand, because a brand is very important so that people are attracted and fascinated by our event and are eager to join it. "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608449547105
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What shutter speed would you use to take a panning shot? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1/30 "
          },
          {
            "question": "A prime lens ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Has a fixed focal length "
          },
          {
            "question": "What does the “bulb” mode in the camera do? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Keeps the shutter open indefinitely "
          },
          {
            "question": "The full frame size DSLR photography refers to frame size ",
            "answer": "\n                                            35mm "
          },
          {
            "question": "The vertical movement of a camera on its axis is called ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tilt "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is the most difficult part of being a photographer for you? ",
            "answer": "As I have a pretty old camera, whenever I try to click photos in low light the image quality is degraded. Thus, it's kind of difficult for me to reduce noise in the image. "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is your favourite lens and why do you prefer it? ",
            "answer": "I don't myself, have a prime lens but I am actually quite fascinated by it. It's very compact and has a wide aperture which allows bokeh. Also, the image quality is quite good."
          },
          {
            "question": " What equipment would you use to take long exposures in a bright lighting condition? ",
            "answer": "The equipment which we require are:\n1. A steady tripod\n2. A camera with very low iso\n3. "
          },
          {
            "question": " How is Depth of Field related to aperture? ",
            "answer": "When we increase the aperture the depth of field reduces or becomes shallow. Whereas decreasing the aperture, the depth of the field becomes deeper."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608450465266
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608446792782
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608448043337
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608449560949
      }
    ],
    "username": "sahil.garg2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 8130028675,
    "first_name": "Sahil",
    "last_name": "Garg",
    "registration": "20BDS0174"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recursion is the phenomenon in which the function calls itself through the calling function statement written within its braces. This is normally done under a condition so that it does not keep calling itself infinitely and throw an error. "
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "Yes it can be called. "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608451396069
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608450199960
      }
    ],
    "username": "niladri.mitra2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9051065549,
    "first_name": "Niladri ",
    "last_name": "Mitra",
    "registration": "20BIT0381"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "Using technology is the only solution to advertise during this pandemic situation\n1. Instagram is the best platform to advertise and connect with students, hence holding live qna in would be a great option.\n2. Forming discord group and presenting the ideas and objective of the club is another option.\n3. Youtube streaming and live webinars are pretty useful too. "
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "Being a part of club is all about teamwork and togetherness. Being violent is not a solution, so ill try my best to peacefully explain the person who doesn't work about the importance of contribution."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "1stly , ill make sure there is no such mistakes made beforehand to avoid havoc in the last moment. if such situation take"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "sponsors don't just provide finances but they also attach their brand value and image. this enhances the reliability factor of the event and will certainly attract more people.\nfactors to keep in mind:\n1. will prefer less popular brands as it will be easy to approach them.\n2. make sure they are well know among the masses.\n3. have the capability to provide good sum of money."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "i would prefer calling the new startup which is growing rapidly because they will be easier to approach and h=can give good insights about how to grow a new startup from scratch."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "It will be great if we can come up with something unique and creative as it will attract more people. however if there is time constraint, it is better to follow standard procedure rather than taking risk in the last moment."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "ONLINE MODE: various social media platforms, such as Instagram, Discord, telegram, WhatsApp etc. \nOFFLINE MODE: word of mouth plays the best role here. also sharing pamphlets and notices is a good option."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "1stly ill not keep my academic preparation pending at the last moment and try to prepare everything beforehand so that I don't face any problem in managing chapter and college work. i will try my best to devote time for chapter (provided it is something extremely urgent)"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "well medical emergency is a serious situation, so i will compensate by giving a speech myself or take help of our technical team to present something interesting in front of the crowd. i will also make sure to apologize the participants and explain them the situation before the event starts."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I am not planning to take part in too many clubs and chapters. At max want to be a part of 2, to avoid clashing of events. incase i have multiple meetings at the same time, divide half time to both the clubs as i can not let them down."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "i will try my best to convince them, but if they don't ill do the work on my own and ask help from some other member of the club who will be free at that particular time. "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608448704660
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608447201141
      }
    ],
    "username": "priyanka.chowdhury2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 919910052839,
    "first_name": "Priyanka ",
    "last_name": "Chowdhury ",
    "registration": "20BIT0197"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "defining problems interms of itself"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608449814343
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608448642017
      }
    ],
    "username": "mohamedfaheem.firoz2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9539178386,
    "first_name": "mohamed faheem ",
    "last_name": "firoz",
    "registration": "20MID0051"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608448635596
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608447432721
      }
    ],
    "username": "dhruv.choudhary2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8448531023,
    "first_name": "Dhruv",
    "last_name": "Choudhary",
    "registration": "19BCE0864"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. in this current situation, social media is one of the best way to publicize the event .\n2. Making catchy posters .\n3. For getting the attention , keeping some prizes or giving opportunity to learn something new is pretty good .  "
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I think in this situation the best way is to communicate with my peer , trying to understand why he is not interested in working with me . Being humble , patient , good listener will work most of the time . Trying to resolve the communication gap between him and me will my priority .  "
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "Things which i can do are:\n1. I'll try my level best to get the auditorium if not possible then\n2. I'll try to arrange some another auditorium , like working with amphitheatre arranging everything there . \n3. last option , if nothing works postponing event will be the last option .\nbeing patient, calm , swift in this situation is a key , and as an organizer i would be accountable and responsible \nPreventing this kind of situation : I would like to re-check with auditorium several times , communicating things clearly would my priority ."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "1. Enforcing more people to maintain the discipline.\n2. trying to get a bigger place if possible .\n3. if the registration exceeds drastically then last option would be cancel and stop the registration , this would be last option , i would not prefer ant participant to be disappointed and at same point maintaining the discipline and smooth conduction of event will be my priority . "
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "without sponsorship conducting a big event is not possible .Sponsorship is the backbone of large scale event . I would like to get sponsors which relate to the event or sponsors which can be related to the youth . \nScale of event and requirements for the event will be my factor to go for sponsorship ."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "If speaker from company A have been invited then i would prefer speaker from company B as it will be inspiration for students and we can learns a lot "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608449407118
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608447904300
      }
    ],
    "username": "shubham.tiwari2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9310592843,
    "first_name": "Shubham",
    "last_name": "Tiwari",
    "registration": "20BCB0121"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608449111891
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608448503505
      }
    ],
    "username": "pratyush.sanadhya2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9601130070,
    "first_name": "Pratyush ",
    "last_name": "Sanadhya",
    "registration": "20BCE0620"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recurssion is a function calling itself inside itself"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608450943734
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "We can increase the resistance in a circuit by using and connecting more loads in the series pattern."
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "GND pins are known as ground pins in Arduino.\nThe ground is always necessary in a circuit for protection purposes."
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "8 to 13"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Face recognition\nProximity sensor\nFingerprint sensor\nTouch sensors"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608451844533
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608449737766
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608451021144
      }
    ],
    "username": "rishit.anand2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 7619377148,
    "first_name": "RISHIT",
    "last_name": "ANAND",
    "registration": "20BCE2146"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608449164969
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608449034592
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608449183509
      }
    ],
    "username": "ankit.kishan2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 9556519339,
    "first_name": "ANKIT",
    "last_name": "KISHAN",
    "registration": "20BEC0193"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "FUNCTION CALLING ITSELF"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "no"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608450752421
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608449548648
      }
    ],
    "username": "tanishq.tyagi2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9837885503,
    "first_name": "Tanishq",
    "last_name": "Tyagi",
    "registration": "20BIT0192"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "increasing the length of the wire or decrease the diameter of the wire"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "motion sensors, gyroscope, proximity sensor, light sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608450855918
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608449932768
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608450256349
      }
    ],
    "username": "sneha.gopalakrishnan2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 8106223291,
    "first_name": "Sneha",
    "last_name": "Gopalakrishnan",
    "registration": "20BEC0504"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608452178256
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608450975405
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608452196281
      }
    ],
    "username": "mohd.anas2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 9654083434,
    "first_name": "MOHD",
    "last_name": "ANAS",
    "registration": "20BCT0350"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "we can small handmade postcards or a simple post on instagram handles"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "i will give him/her two options either he/she could leave formally or could agree with some of our points"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "see before hand i will try to look the schedule myself and confirming everything is good and if this situation occurs i will try to find a new audi or i will change the time or either talk to other people but this kind of situations wont occur at first place"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "i will try to talk with the venue coordinator for the necessary increase or then i will try my best to organize a new place"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "sponsorships is basically marketing so that they could invite more people to their place hence it is a mutual help that both the parties could be benefited"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "company b obviously because they would have been more prepared and could actually get this as an opportunity"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "yes i think its necessary because we all look upto a good presentation or something unique so that our audience isn't bored by the same standard"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "we can initiate fun games or activities to initiate their products so that people could find interesting because simply speaking about the product wont help so we can go through fun tasks or some small workshop"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "i will first cool myself and would look upon to that where there is much work left would then finanlize which one should i submit "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "within 5 mins i will arrange someone else or would take up myself because wasting someone else time could ruin our event"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "in such a situation i have to prioritise my things and would come to a conclusion that which is more important for me. "
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "since i have to be flexible enough so i will agree to the points and try to manipulate a bit."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608452115648
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608451069406
      }
    ],
    "username": "sheetal.sahoo2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 6394419974,
    "first_name": "sheetal",
    "last_name": "sahoo",
    "registration": "20BEE0066"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true for microcontrollers and microprocessors? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both contain processing unit "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "Heating the wires used can increase resistance. \nUsing very high voltage source for a greater time would increase resistance."
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Accelerometer\nFinger print sensor\nGyroscope\n"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608452046522
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608451109685
      }
    ],
    "username": "shrutisuresh.nair2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 971506013458,
    "first_name": "Shruti",
    "last_name": "Nair",
    "registration": "20BEE0053"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608452343022
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "By advertising the event \nby telling its benefits and generating the curiosity in the domain"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "firstly we need to understand the other point of view why he is not willing to work with me and according to it ill try to. change my point or maybe his point"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "firstly to make sure that this thing never happen again I will double check while  booking and take their confirmation.\nand if this happens so then ill have no other option rather to apologise to the audience and team\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "if the crowd is too much we can arrange some more chair for the crowd or can see for a bigger place for the event or we can make the split the event for two days instead of one day"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for an event because we can't raise so much money by our self and secondly by getting sponsorship sponsors get their company advertise"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "from company B as it a new start up which needs to establish its roots so they will give the sponsorship easily and without any bargain"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "Unique idea is one which attracts people so I will go with the unique idea"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "by putting banners\nby telling the benefits of giving sponsorship"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "I will try to finish with the study of the tomorrow's paper early as possible and then do the chapter's urgent work"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will ask someone else speak "
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "no idea "
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "will try to understand this point and if not ill try him to convince him"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608453416378
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608451518704
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608452388944
      }
    ],
    "username": "shivam.singhal2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9837054546,
    "first_name": "Shivam",
    "last_name": "Singhal",
    "registration": "19BCE2112"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "recursion means using the function again and again to get the required output such as "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608461864635
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608460662307
      }
    ],
    "username": "aman.sharma2020b@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7738400035,
    "first_name": "Aman ",
    "last_name": "Sharma",
    "registration": "20BCT0267"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1.POST IT ON VIT VELLORE OFFICIAL INSTRAGRAM PAGE\n2.COLLABORATION WITH VIT SPOT\n3.USE VIT MEME PAGE TO GET PUBLICITY"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "1.MOTIVATE HIM TO DO WORK TRY TO EXPLAIN THE POWER OF TEAM WORK\n2.POLITE ASK THE LEADER TO TALK TO MEMBER ABOUT HIS PROBLEM"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "TRY TO ARRANGE OTHER AUDITORIUM EVEN IF DOES NOT GIVES US PROPER ARRANGEMENTS"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "TRY TO ARRANGE MOVEABLE CHAIRS OR SHIFT THE EVENT TO BIG AUDI OR TRY TO CONDUCT IN SHIFTS"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "IMPORTANT FOR PRIZE MONEY \nTO PUBLICISE THE EVENT \nTO PROVIDE SERVICES\nSPONSORS SHOULD BE RELATED TO THE EVENT"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "START UP ONE BEACAUSE HE WILL KNOW THE FRESH IDEAS AND KNOWS DEEPLY ABOUT THE MARKET"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "NEW UNIQUE AND CREATIVE"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "KEEP THE PRICE FOR USING COMPANY PRODUCT"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "CHAPTER'S URGENT WORK"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I WILL KEEP A BACK UP SPEAKER"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "NO I AM LOYAL TO ONE CLUB"
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "WE ASK THE OTHERS MEMBER FOR OPINION"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608453329330
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608452226301
      }
    ],
    "username": "utkarsh.trivdi2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7800064493,
    "first_name": "utkarsh",
    "last_name": "trivedi",
    "registration": "19BEC0201"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608453564422
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "YES. sensor()"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "Control the temperature. (increase)"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "They allow maximum current flow."
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "By adding Wifi Module"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "GND"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Infrared(atleast redmi sensor)\nProximity\nAccelerometer\n"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608454323086
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608452361462
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608453585581
      }
    ],
    "username": "krishnadev.g2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 6362181751,
    "first_name": "Krishnadev",
    "last_name": "G",
    "registration": "20BCI0039"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608453561769
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true for microcontrollers and microprocessors? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both contain processing unit "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "Yes"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "Increase temperature"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "They allow max current flow"
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "Wifi MOdule to be attached"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Proximity sensor, accelerometer,compass "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608454331320
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608452357892
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608453577325
      }
    ],
    "username": "gauri.pradeep2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 9620273321,
    "first_name": "Gauri",
    "last_name": "Pradeep",
    "registration": "20BEC0307"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be stored in list1 and list2 if the following code is executed?\nList1=[‘a’,’b’,’c’]\nList1+=’de’\nList2=[1,2,3,4]\nList2+=10 ",
            "answer": "\n                                            [‘a’,’b’,’c’,’d’,’e’],error "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "recursion is a mathematical and programming concept . it means that a function calls itself."
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "no"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608454002701
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be stored in list1 and list2 if the following code is executed?\nList1=[‘a’,’b’,’c’]\nList1+=’de’\nList2=[1,2,3,4]\nList2+=10 ",
            "answer": "\n                                            [‘a’,’b’,’c’,’d’,’e’],error "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "recursion is a mathematical and programming concept . it means that a function calls itself."
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "no"
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "recursion is a mathematical and programming concept . it means that a function calls itself."
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "no"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608454002920
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608453245190
      }
    ],
    "username": "charandeepu.m2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 9503515866,
    "first_name": "Charan",
    "last_name": "Deepu",
    "registration": "20MIS0071"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608453261651
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608453262766
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "I would rate my writing skills a solid 7 due to several reasons. My peers appreciate my writing skills as I can express my thoughts precisely through my writing and grab the reader's attention."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "I love to express my thoughts on a particular matter or subject and see how others react to it, whether they resonate with my line of thought or how different their opinion is.\nAnd writing is the only way i can express these thoughts in a well-structured and thought of manner.\npersonally speaking, i'm not much of a good speaker."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "When I think of technological advancements in the recent times, the most prominent revolution that first strikes my mind  is of the cellphone/smartphone domain.\nDo you recall how phones were just a means to have a voice call with a distant dear one? when no one bothered about the weight, the size, the look, the speed etc. etc? Look how far the industry has come. Now a smartphone(as we call it now) lives up to its name for being smart, now it's not just a calling device, it is your substitute to your computer, calculator, television, radio, camera etc. Now the specs of the device matters, its speed, its RAM, its display all are now a determining factor when you go on to buy one for yourself.\nTHIS IS THE DRAMATIC REVOLUTION, AND THIS SURELY IS THE FUTURE.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "LEARNING HOW A MACHINE LEARNS\nHOW IT AUTOMATES ALL OF YOUR TASKS \nAN APP THAT RECOGNISES YOUR IMAGE FROM THE GROUP OF 40!\nDOESN'T THAT INTRIGUE YOU?\n\nwell if it does and you would like to try your hands upon this stunning technology , then you do not want to miss out on this opportunity.\n\nWe here at IETE chapter present to you the event\n\"Machine Learning basics\" the link for which would be available on our instagram page.\nDate: December 28, 2020\nStay tuned for more updates!"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608455100512
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. By indulging the members of the chapters to spread the good word about our chapter in their respective class groups, by telling the advantages of the events.\n2. Interacting with the students on all social media and solving all their queries  regarding the event, making them feel comfortable with the chapter and hence building their trust.\n3. Organize small  meetup sessions with students interested in order to get familiar with them and so that they can open up easily and ask their queries and clear their confusion"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I would ask them about why aren't they willing to co-ordinate or work. After finding the root cause i would look for possible solution which is acceptable by the whole team with certain small compromises on everyone's part.\nThe basic motive is to find a middle ground of all the demands and problems as we have to look for the entire team and not only for an individual."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "Firstly, I would immediately meet up with the other event coordinators and without discussing why the confusion arose, my priority would be how to deal with this now.\none possible solution that comes to my mind is to discuss the duration of their events and at what time have they organized their event to be conducted. And whether or not can they compromise on that time , like rescheduling it to a later time on the same day. As my event is almost within 2 hours and it would be too late to reschedule it. \nEven trimming down the length of the event could be used as a last resort.\nwe would put up a display board outside the event room/hall. About the rescheduled timing of the events with an apology for the inconvenience caused.\n\nI believe the cause for this confusion would have been caused by the person/committee responsible for assigning the hall to the clubs/chapters. For it to be never repeated again i would advise them to make a proper record of which team has been assigned which hall/room and should re-check with them atleast 2 days before the e  "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608457237188
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608452775476
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608453296834
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608455733476
      }
    ],
    "username": "shivang.singh2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 7,
    "contact_number": 919650229309,
    "first_name": "Shivang",
    "last_name": "Singh",
    "registration": "20BEC0239"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608458710284
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608457506213
      }
    ],
    "username": "madanagopal.c2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9629213140,
    "first_name": "Madanagopal",
    "last_name": "C",
    "registration": "20BCE0602"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "when a function calls itself "
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "yes"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608454928253
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608453724044
      }
    ],
    "username": "kunal.vijay2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8178050765,
    "first_name": "Kunal ",
    "last_name": "Vijay ",
    "registration": "20BCI0122"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "Yes, it can call,by using public method inside that class."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608456425007
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608455218518
      }
    ],
    "username": "charchit.mangal2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7568468472,
    "first_name": "Charchit",
    "last_name": "Mangal",
    "registration": "20BBS0204"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "9 because I really believe that there is always a scope for improvement and I like to  inculcate various domains in my writing which helps me evolve and improve at the same time"
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "The desire to learn better, expression of views and ideas and most importantly spreading awareness among people motivates me to write and evolve to a great extent."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "3-D PRINTER- \nThe human race has always innovated, and in a relatively short time went from building fires and making stone-tipped arrows to creating smartphone apps and autonomous robots. Today, technological advancement has undoubtedly contributed to a change in the way we work, live and survive in the coming decades. The convergence of cheaper manufacturing methods and open source software has led to a revolution of 3-D printing in recent years."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "Greetings from IETE!\n'Interested in predictive analysis? Then research artificial intelligence,\nmachine learning and deep learning!' \nAre you interested in machine learning and its applications? Don't worry IETE Club has a solution!\nWe are glad to announce that we are organizing a workshop on 'Machine Learning' on 28th December'2020.\nPlatform-MS teams\nTiming-5:00 pm"
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "Making my parents proud is the biggest accomplishment according to me. No matter how much you achieve, if they are happy, your achievement is worth it. I made them proud during the board and JEE results and that gives me utmost satisfaction!"
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "According to me, organizing yourself is the most important task. You have to be pre planned about whatever you do. If it is not planned, there is no point in doing it. Making to do list, making a proper timetable and prioritizing the most important task is the key to a stable routine."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "The technical domains of IETE and the various aspects of management and editorial venture fascinated me to a great extent which is the main reason to apply for this club. I feel that IETE would provide me a platform to improve and evolve at the same time!"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608457356514
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608455713489
      }
    ],
    "username": "ananya.2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9140908930,
    "first_name": "Ananya",
    "last_name": "Verma",
    "registration": "20BEC0202"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608458101076
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608458101486
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608458102467
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608458103231
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608458103624
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608458103893
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608458104248
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608458104697
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608456091630
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608457187834
      }
    ],
    "username": "saurabh.singh2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 10,
    "contact_number": 6377288941,
    "first_name": "SAURABH",
    "last_name": "SINGH",
    "registration": "19BCI0184"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "When you make solve a problem from using the problem itself then we can call it as recurssion"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "No a private function can't call a protected variable."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608458166616
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608457043814
      }
    ],
    "username": "aneesh.panda2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7780566528,
    "first_name": "Aneesh",
    "last_name": "Panda",
    "registration": "20BKT0088"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be stored in list1 and list2 if the following code is executed?\nList1=[‘a’,’b’,’c’]\nList1+=’de’\nList2=[1,2,3,4]\nList2+=10 ",
            "answer": "\n                                            [‘a’,’b’,’c’,’d’,’e’],error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608467839755
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608466636463
      }
    ],
    "username": "athiya.m2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9384662784,
    "first_name": "Athiya",
    "last_name": "M",
    "registration": "20BKT0042"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "recursion is nothing but executing the same code repeatedly until the base condition satisfys"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "not possible"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608457513077
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608456308721
      }
    ],
    "username": "kushwanth.sai2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8688546118,
    "first_name": "kushwanth",
    "last_name": "sai",
    "registration": "19BCT0149"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "calling a fun "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608457958899
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608456754200
      }
    ],
    "username": "rishabhkumar.rai2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7080147006,
    "first_name": "Rishabh Kumar",
    "last_name": "Rai",
    "registration": "20BKT0076"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "Publicizing through social media platforms\nCreate a Youtube channel\nUsing online advertising tools\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I would convince the person that it is a matter of pride for our entire college and not just ourselves so we can keep our grudges aside and work together. I can persuade my friends to talk to that person and convince him/her."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "I will immediately inform the authorities and ask them for an alternative venue where no event is taking place. I will ensure that the same doesn't get repeated by making calls a day prior to the event and checking the venue list of all other events that are taking place on the same day."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I will make sure that no repeated names are there in the list. If the exceeded registrations are around 10-15 then I will include those students as well otherwise I'll consider the students who had filled the form on time."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors improve the event's image and broaden the competitiveness. They also offer funding to support the event.\nKey factors:\nbudget\nno of participants\nvenue"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "Company B because it is a new start-up and is already growing rapidly. The members might have better plans and ideas than company A. We have already interacted with company A members so this time we can try out something new."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "Following the standard procedure could be monotonous and our team members wouldn't enjoy it too. To keep the event interactive and fun-filled, it's better to think of creative ideas."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "Promote their product/service through plays, music sessions, jingles, etc. Use social media to promote their service. Conduct interviews with the sponsorship team."
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Time management is the key factor in prioritizing our work. I will ensure that I don't leave my preparation for the last day. I can ask for help from other members of the chapter as well. I will divide the work between the members so no one gets pressurized."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I will look for an alternative individual who is good at speaking and can handle the situation well. We can delay the event by some time and look for possible back up plans. "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608458480346
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "by changing the wire material, by making a series connection."
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "gyroscope\nfingerprint sensor\nposture sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608459495408
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608456977589
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608458650993
      }
    ],
    "username": "rehmamanaal.rizvi2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 8601382024,
    "first_name": "Rehma",
    "last_name": "Rizvi",
    "registration": "20BEE0042"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. online events can be conducted because it is playing a prominent role during covid-19\n2. also one of the most effective ways to reach out to students is by email marketing where interested students will get regular updates about the event in their mail ids.\n3. finally social media platform like instagram and twitter can play an important role here."
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "its human nature for people to make assumptions about someone else's behavior in order to overcome this situation i will  contact my friends and discuss about the issues so that the leader can take an initiative and switch my team"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "to avoid a situation like this it is important for the club members to have a proper approach towards how and when the event is going to be conducted.its also important for the team head to prebook the auditorium before any other causes any discrepancies."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "if the number of registrations crosses the maximum capacity i'll conduct the session in two slots . so that people will be able to utilize the maximum knowledge they gain from it rather than denying them from attending the event."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "sponsorship is necessary for an organisation because it helps to increase the financial accountability of the club and it will also help to increase the public image in various fields."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "i would choose company A because people tend to be more interested towards speakers from reputed organisation rather than the start ups because this will give an oppurtunity to increase the public image of the chapter too."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "it is always better to get some unique ideas because people don't like monotonous things and they prefer interesting things over the repeated ones"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "we can run a social media contests to publicize the product in the online mode and in the offline mode we can host an event or offer complimentary upgrades instead of the product"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "inorder to prioritize anything it is important to note that we always need to balance between things rather than prioritizing. which means we need to put in extra efforts and give value to both of the works . this can be done by making a list which contains all the task to be done ."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "we need to be prepared for anything . to tackle this situation we can communicate with the attendees and consider some refund policy instead of keeping them in the dark."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "i would let the team head of one of the clubs/chapters to know about the situation beforehand instead of skipping it and attend the club/chapter which requires utmost help and guidance ."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "opinions are never wrong . the members just represent a way one percieves things and after all we are trying to teach only one another right? if a situation like this arises its essential to listen to others point of view first and stay calm instead jumping into something."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608460802963
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608459446515
      }
    ],
    "username": "bhavya.bhan2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7989133285,
    "first_name": "Bhavya",
    "last_name": "Bhan",
    "registration": "20mid0082"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "When a fn calls itself it's called recursion. There should be base case to stop the calling of the fn , otherwise, infinite loop"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608458389455
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608457186274
      }
    ],
    "username": "vishnu.ramkumar2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9445201970,
    "first_name": "Vishnu",
    "last_name": "Ramkumar",
    "registration": "20BDS0250"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608459097812
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608459097849
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "resistance can be increases by increasing the length of circuit wire of decreasing the area of circuit wire"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608459954590
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "One of the best way is to use social platforms like instagram . Students use instagram a lot these days and will definitely see your advertisement\nSecond way would be to take numbers from MS teams and send message to their whatsapp with attractive posters and achievements\nThird way would be to email them in university mail as everyone checks mail if there is something important...mail is also available in MS teams"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "Well work can still be done in such situations its just that it will take extra effort . But if we really want our team to perform well then we will have to take up that extra effort to do well. "
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "We have 1 hr 30 min time. As an co ordinator I will definitely prepare for such events and prepare back up. 1hr 30 min is a lot of time and by arranging transport facility for audience we can easily conduct at the back up place. We can also go for online event as it doesnt require auditorium"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Money is always required for conducting an event and hence sponsors play a huge role here. Also if the event in sponsored by some brand then people feel that this is not just an casual event. Hence sponsors play this role as well. \nFor an organization to be sponsor the image of that oragnization should be good in market and its product must be something that people fill interesting as this grabs attention of audience "
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would chose company B as in this time start ups are getting very popular and is a mark that we are open to modern thoughts. This will also attract young audience as many of them will be trying start ups themselves and could inspire them and also get to learn something"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "If we go with standard ideas then we have to make sure that all arrangements are up tp the mark as these are the times where unique and creative ideas are grabbing attention.  But still if the event is conducted with perfection then its all good. \nUsing unique ideas are also a good option but it has to be interesting "
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "Best way of publicizing of products and services in such times is using online platforms like instagram and snapchat. This way your service will definitely grab attention. Advertisement in OTT platforms and movie watching websites can also work wonders.\nFor offline advertisement we can opt for hoarding near malls and restaurants as such places are often visited and hence viewed by people"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "Theres always enough time if you really wish to do. If i have some chapters urgent work then i will definitely finish that first because i am joining chapter because i commit myself fully to it in hard times, Also studies can be done late by staying up"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "If i am co ordinator of any event then i will always have back up for such cases. Thats what good co ordinators do. Also in such cases we can request audience to wait for some time and meanwhile arrange for a speaker as co ordinator have strong network."
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "We have to set our priorities. If one club/chapters work will fall drastically by my absence then i will chose to be a part of that club. Nothing is impossible with proper planning. "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608461495530
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608457916482
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608459678524
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608459992085
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608461510848
      }
    ],
    "username": "archit.jain2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 8,
    "contact_number": 9752296666,
    "first_name": "Archit",
    "last_name": "Jain",
    "registration": "20BCE0642"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "I will rate it 8 out of 10 as I have been a critic of social issues and have been a thorough watcher of the society, it's people and politics. So, I do also have good editorial capacity. I rated it 2 marks less because my vocabulary, which is in a thriving stage itself. "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "Simply my ethical perception and conscience motivates myself to write. As they say in a popular hindi quote, When you want to bring revolution don't go for a sword; go for a pen and a paper."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "First it is communication asset's reformation. Revolution in Telecommunication and networking has the highest impact on the society. Advancement of vehicles which uses non carbon fuel. Block chain Technology has made the assets of people more safer virtually. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "\" Don't always indulge in the machines and let them waste your time. Learn them and make them run on your commands.\"\n\nWe will be waiting for you in the XYZ Block on 28th of December.\nSee you there."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I haven't accomplished much big things in my life. But It was a achievement for me to get a seat in VIT with a good rank, which was a dream of mine."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "There are two factors. First is to focus on the task, on which I am working. And second is to be patient. Planning of a work simply could be done by focusing on it. We should then prioritize the work on the basis of how much time it takes to be completed and patiently finish one after another."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "I have been a follower of the club from last few days and I saw the work that it does and loved it. I had also taken part in one of its workshop's in the Gravitas' events. Editing is my hobby, basically which motivates me for the club."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608459524017
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "I will rate it 8 out of 10 as I have been a critic of social issues and have been a thorough watcher of the society, it's people and politics. So, I do also have good editorial capacity. I rated it 2 marks less because my vocabulary, which is in a thriving stage itself. "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "Simply my ethical perception and conscience motivates myself to write. As they say in a popular hindi quote, When you want to bring revolution don't go for a sword; go for a pen and a paper."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "First it is communication asset's reformation. Revolution in Telecommunication and networking has the highest impact on the society. Advancement of vehicles which uses non carbon fuel. Block chain Technology has made the assets of people more safer virtually. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "\" Don't always indulge in the machines and let them waste your time. Learn them and make them run on your commands.\"\n\nWe will be waiting for you in the XYZ Block on 28th of December.\nSee you there."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I haven't accomplished much big things in my life. But It was a achievement for me to get a seat in VIT with a good rank, which was a dream of mine."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "There are two factors. First is to focus on the task, on which I am working. And second is to be patient. Planning of a work simply could be done by focusing on it. We should then prioritize the work on the basis of how much time it takes to be completed and patiently finish one after another."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "I have been a follower of the club from last few days and I saw the work that it does and loved it. I had also taken part in one of its workshop's in the Gravitas' events. Editing is my hobby, basically which motivates me for the club."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "I will rate it 8 out of 10 as I have been a critic of social issues and have been a thorough watcher of the society, it's people and politics. So, I do also have good editorial capacity. I rated it 2 marks less because my vocabulary, which is in a thriving stage itself. "
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivates you to write? ",
            "answer": "Simply my ethical perception and conscience motivates myself to write. As they say in a popular hindi quote, When you want to bring revolution don't go for a sword; go for a pen and a paper."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write 50 words on any technological advancement in the 21st century. ",
            "answer": "First it is communication asset's reformation. Revolution in Telecommunication and networking has the highest impact on the society. Advancement of vehicles which uses non carbon fuel. Block chain Technology has made the assets of people more safer virtually. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Write a caption for an event on Machine Learning which would take place on 28th December. Write a suitable title and mention the time and platform according to your wish. ",
            "answer": "\" Don't always indulge in the machines and let them waste your time. Learn them and make them run on your commands.\"\n\nWe will be waiting for you in the XYZ Block on 28th of December.\nSee you there."
          },
          {
            "question": "Write about an accomplishment you are most proud of in 30 words. ",
            "answer": "I haven't accomplished much big things in my life. But It was a achievement for me to get a seat in VIT with a good rank, which was a dream of mine."
          },
          {
            "question": "How do you organize, plan, and prioritize your work? ",
            "answer": "There are two factors. First is to focus on the task, on which I am working. And second is to be patient. Planning of a work simply could be done by focusing on it. We should then prioritize the work on the basis of how much time it takes to be completed and patiently finish one after another."
          },
          {
            "question": "What motivated you to apply for IETE's editorial team? ",
            "answer": "I have been a follower of the club from last few days and I saw the work that it does and loved it. I had also taken part in one of its workshop's in the Gravitas' events. Editing is my hobby, basically which motivates me for the club."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608459524425
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608457725572
      }
    ],
    "username": "amit.priyadarshi2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 7735629090,
    "first_name": "Amit",
    "last_name": "Priyadarshi",
    "registration": "20BIT0196 "
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. we can use various social media platforms and posts \n2. use several hastags in social media\n3. use various attractitive digital flyers,posters etc and make short videos to advertise our event "
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "i would like to motive my team members regarding their importance in the team. i will try to figure out all the issues i have with that member.i will make sure to convince him work in the team. even if he donnot agree ,i will try to put up his ideas because we need the team to be united and not broken. so o would compromise if his idea is worthy."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "i will try to produce all the proofs and paperworks done for finalizing the auditorium for our event. meanwhile i will ask other teammates to arr5ange for differ3nt locations where we can host the event .if we donnot get back the auditorium then we will host it in thw new place and spread the news of the new location through various platforms .i would always have video and paperwork proofs to avoid such issues."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "when the number of registrations will increase ,i will try to cancel their registration because i want to put up a quality event with limited peoples but full of praises rather than more more peoiple with hatred for the event\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "yes sponsors are cfrucial for a event .they provide all the money and variuos equipments with which we can run the event smoothly and efficiently."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "we will getting speaker from company B because it will save our funds  and audeience will also be more enthusistic to hear a new speaker ,the speaker will give try to give his best because he will try to make a good name and improve himself,we will also have a huge crowd."
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "yes ,it is necessary to come up new ideas  to organise an event . i would use social media as a major asset to go through it because people will get to learn something new and we will have more audience.the team members will also workn with more zeal because of the changes."
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "we can us ethe sponsrs names in t-shiryts,hoodies, we can put up the name in the stage,ask the anchors to take the sponsor names repeatativly and use social media as well\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "i will try my best to manage both with the help of proper time management."
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "i will find othe rsolution for it.i will have many backups plans because such things cannot be stopped from the beginning .i will arrange for my backup speaker to speak .in the meanwhile we will engage the audience by playing some music or just by interacting with them. "
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "i will priotiyize my things .i will try to take part in a place which needs me the3 most at that particular moment and so that i can attend both the meetings and it will be a successful one."
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "when my other members are not agreeing ,then i will try to explain them where thay are wrong and tell them to work as a team .if their ideas will be better then i will implement those. but if then they donnot agree i will compromise with my plans."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608459536525
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608458300196
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608459813565
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608459842004
      }
    ],
    "username": "bidwan.rath2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 7683816012,
    "first_name": "Bidwan",
    "last_name": "Rath",
    "registration": "20BCE0681 "
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "longer wire"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "To close electric circuit."
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "Launch , connect to pc, toggle ports and upload ESP"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "Rx,Tx"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Ambient light sensor, Compass, Hall effect, Fingerprint sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608461107494
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "defining a problem in terms of itself, also called process of repeating itself."
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "Yes it can called."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608480998887
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608458597331
      },
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608459904146
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608479795056
      }
    ],
    "username": "dattakumar.malkhede2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 5,
    "contact_number": 7385857117,
    "first_name": "Dattakumar",
    "last_name": "Malkhede",
    "registration": "20MES0051"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recursion basically means \"calling itself\"."
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "A protected variable can't be accessed by users of the class but can be accessed inside a subclass that inherits from the class."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608459842104
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608458676841
      }
    ],
    "username": "utkarsh.shukla2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 918082924156,
    "first_name": "Utkarsh",
    "last_name": "Shukla",
    "registration": "19BCI0099"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "recursion is the process in which function call it self until the requirement is not fulfilled or the termination condition is not reached."
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "yes "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608460013622
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608458841499
      }
    ],
    "username": "dharmendra.kumar2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9165584988,
    "first_name": "DHARMENDRA KUMAR ",
    "last_name": "PRASAD",
    "registration": "20MCA0112"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608467210841
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608466437956
      }
    ],
    "username": "anoushka.shresth2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7490021818,
    "first_name": "anoushka",
    "last_name": "shresth",
    "registration": "20BCE2305"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true for microcontrollers and microprocessors? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both contain processing unit "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "no, we only declare ping and echo pins"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "builtin resistance in arduino"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "to connect the sensor or componetnt to ground, if using multipe grounds  we can common the ground"
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": " a esp8266 module"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "key"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "acclerometer, light dectector, camera "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608463099730
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608461914117
      }
    ],
    "username": "vaddiraju.abhinav2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 919908597175,
    "first_name": "Abhinav",
    "last_name": "Vaddiraju",
    "registration": "19BEC0755"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true for microcontrollers and microprocessors? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both contain processing unit "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "thick wire"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "fingerprint sensor\ncompass\nproximity sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608465384924
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "a defined function can call itself."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608467151999
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608464540745
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608465396349
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608466199387
      }
    ],
    "username": "arjeet.anand2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 5,
    "contact_number": 7004253767,
    "first_name": "Arjeet",
    "last_name": "Anand",
    "registration": "20BEC0599"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be stored in list1 and list2 if the following code is executed?\nList1=[‘a’,’b’,’c’]\nList1+=’de’\nList2=[1,2,3,4]\nList2+=10 ",
            "answer": "\n                                            [‘a’,’b’,’c’,’d’,’e’],error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608467003809
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608465794273
      }
    ],
    "username": "mugdharaje.ashiya2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7627006100,
    "first_name": "Mugdha",
    "last_name": "Raje Ashiya",
    "registration": "20BDS0204"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the size of char and int data types respectively? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 byte, Compiler dependent "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Repetition of a particular statement.Eg; used in case of loops"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "Yes"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608481235349
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608480032040
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608481246169
      }
    ],
    "username": "irene.john2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 7306086063,
    "first_name": "Irene",
    "last_name": "John",
    "registration": "19BCE2437"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "void main()\n{\nfloat x = 0.1;\nif(x==0.1){\nprintf(“IETE-ISF”);\nprintf(“%f ”,x);\n}\nelse{\nprintf(“IETE”);\nprintf(“%d”,x);\n}\n}\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            IETE Junk Value "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "a function is called by itself is called as recursion"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "no"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608468698977
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608467495242
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608468755399
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608468777593
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608468790053
      },
      {
        "domain": "photography",
        "startTime": 1608468801697
      }
    ],
    "username": "vaishnavi.selvakasi2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 7708682888,
    "first_name": "Vaishnavi",
    "last_name": "Selvakasi",
    "registration": "20BCE2756"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "New ping  library "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "capacitor "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "GND it takes the excess current "
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "we can use esp8266 module "
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "rx and tx pins"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "proximity sensor\ntouch sensor\naccelerometer\ngyroscope\nfingerprint sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608471288908
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "RGB is to ppi as CMYK is to _.\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Dots per inch "
          },
          {
            "question": "How is a color scheme different from color selection? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Schemes are pairings of colors that work well together. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "yes Adobe photoshop"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "png  have good quality when compared to jpg "
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "press control and  select two layer \nright click and select merge layers "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "To improve my design knowledge and skills. I will use  pre-existing \nbackground(stock images)and modify it "
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "I will try asking help from others  to help out with my works and always I try to complete my work on time "
          },
          {
            "question": "Attach any of your previous work (at least 1) in the attachment below. (can be Event\nposters, Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video Editing, etc.) [ADD A DRIVE LINK] ",
            "answer": "https://drive.google.com/drive/u/2/folders/1dTttpP9QPRtak6gr7xpGRzdrWrMK7VT1"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608473090242
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "RGB is to ppi as CMYK is to _.\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Dots per inch "
          },
          {
            "question": "How is a color scheme different from color selection? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Schemes are pairings of colors that work well together. "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "yes Adobe photoshop"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "png  have good quality when compared to jpg "
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "press control and  select two layer \nright click and select merge layers "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "To improve my design knowledge and skills. I will use  pre-existing \nbackground(stock images)and modify it "
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "I will try asking help from others  to help out with my works and always I try to complete my work on time "
          },
          {
            "question": "Attach any of your previous work (at least 1) in the attachment below. (can be Event\nposters, Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video Editing, etc.) [ADD A DRIVE LINK] ",
            "answer": "https://drive.google.com/drive/u/2/folders/1dTttpP9QPRtak6gr7xpGRzdrWrMK7VT1"
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "yes Adobe photoshop"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "png  have good quality when compared to jpg "
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "press control and  select two layer \nright click and select merge layers "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "To improve my design knowledge and skills. I will use  pre-existing \nbackground(stock images)and modify it "
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "I will try asking help from others  to help out with my works and always I try to complete my work on time "
          },
          {
            "question": "Attach any of your previous work (at least 1) in the attachment below. (can be Event\nposters, Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video Editing, etc.) [ADD A DRIVE LINK] ",
            "answer": "https://drive.google.com/drive/u/2/folders/1dTttpP9QPRtak6gr7xpGRzdrWrMK7VT1"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608473091159
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608473091820
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608470084134
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608471490396
      }
    ],
    "username": "tarun.s2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 9080806506,
    "first_name": "Tarun",
    "last_name": "Shanmugam",
    "registration": "19BEI0078"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. Groups can be made on WhatsApp and discord. This would provide an appropriate platform to address the queries of the students and build hype around the events.\n2. Live events on YouTube and Microsoft Teams can be organized to draw the interest and attention of students.\n3. Bulk SMS is another option that can be used."
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I would try to gauge the reason behind the resistance of that team member to work with me and talk to him upfront about the issue and apologize if I find that something I said offended him/her. I would next look for the opportunity to help him so that he/she would owe me a favor and that would completely break the ice between us."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "To make sure that something like this never happens I would \n1.Assign more than one person the task to make sure that all the arrangements have been made and to check for discrepancies.\n2. I would book the auditorium for an hour more than the planned duration of the event.\n3. I would remain on good terms with my teachers as well as maintain a good equation with board members of other teams.\nIn case if such a mistake does happen, the best solution would be to either hold the event on a rooftop or arrange it in classroom."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "First of all, just because everyone has registered for the event doesn't mean that everyone is going to necessarily attend the event. The extra registrations can be put on a waitlist till a seat frees up for them. A live telecast o YouTube live can also be organized for the extra attendees. The attendees can be asked in good spirit to notify at least 12 hours in advance if they are unable to attend the event."
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors are crucial for an event because an event needs money for venue, furniture, snacks and beverages, prizes, event t shirts, stationary, travel and transport, marketing, social media promotion, photographers, posters, audio and video, wifi as well as internet supply which a student run organization can't afford by itself.\nthe key factors to keep in mind while approaching an organization for sponsorship are:\n1. Their good will among other student clubs and chapters.\n2. Their reputation in the market.\n3. Their financial statements that are publicly available."
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I would invite a speaker from company B because I feel that as part of an engineering college many students dream of having their own startups and being complete novices to the professional world, they will be able to relate more and learn more from a speaker from a new but rapidly growing startup"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "An event is an event because it is special. It is important to come up with an unique idea because that not only pushes the organizers to strive for better quality with lesser budget than the previous ones but also build excitement among the attendees about the event."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608482391278
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608480886195
      }
    ],
    "username": "anmol.gupta2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 8797303509,
    "first_name": "ANMOL",
    "last_name": "GUPTA",
    "registration": "20BCB0135"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. using the platforms like WhatsApp rather than Instagram or Facebook as messages spread more quickly on WhatsApp\n2. announcing some events in which there are chances of winning anyone rather a beginner or an advanced level person in that skill\n3. bringing people from the field who came up like rising stars from the mentorship provided through the chapter"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "first, I would ask him what is the issue that he doesn't want to work with me and would try to resolve that issue but if still, he is uncomfortable then it depends on the situation whether I would step back and let someone else do it or I would carry on with his disliking towards me"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "to take care of the situation i will try to contact the person organizing the other event and request him if he could postpone it \nsimultaneously I will try to book another venue and call the creative team to change the venue on the invitation if I am able to get a booking and would send an apology to every guest invited there for the minute inconvenience \nIn the future, I will make sure to call and check for the bookings one week and one day before the event"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "i  such a case firstly i would try to arrange a new place as venue \nif not possible then i would try to make some arrangments for the extra guests their itself \nlast option is to either Livestream the event or doing one more such kind of event in near future with more guest capacity"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "sponsors are  crucial for events as they provide with financial help so that the event goes smooth\nto decide a sponsor first its name shouldn't be something awkward that the people would not like to see\nthe event should benfit teh sponsors also else they would never agree again to sponsor in other events"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "i would like to get a speaker from company B as he/she would be focusing on the current trends and would bring up with some new challenges faced by them during this time"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "comping up with a unique idea is beneficial as peopleget bored seeing the same thing every where so they would love to see some thing new"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "if teh sponsors products are relalated to teh events then they can be advertised by using them in the event if not then there can be banners posters and the hosts advertising for them"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "it completely depends on the situation whether I am well prepared for the exam or not"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "we can bring up the alternative speaker as all the good event organizers keep a backup and if not then it would be best to say sorry and arrange a new event or return th"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608471982792
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "RGB is to ppi as CMYK is to _.\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Dots per inch "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "i ahve editied a sort film for my team \nsoftware used us adobe premier pro"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "png has a lossless compresion\njpg has a lossy compresion"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608472262210
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608470479792
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608472010246
      }
    ],
    "username": "anuj.chaudhary2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 4,
    "contact_number": 8851290852,
    "first_name": "Anuj",
    "last_name": "Chaudhary",
    "registration": "20BCE0998"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "one way would be through the social media.This is the most prominent and efficient way of reaching the masses.\nAlso making the members of the club to atleast inform some fixed number of students from our college and checking on the for the same.\nthe next way would be publishing the same through other club portals tooo."
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "well, I would try finding out the reason behind it and try to solve it and makes sure the person feels comfortable working with me.\nIn the worst case,if thats not  possible i would try other altenatives such as changing the person to other group or something."
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "I'll try convincing the authorities for the event location and at the same time will be looking for some other location for the event to be conducted.\nAnd I  guess its the person assigned for the event responsibility to make sure everything is organized beforehand and make sure everything is organized perfectly.\nIf i would be the person, i I would make sure the location and all other required things are well in place atleast a few days before the event .\nand at the same time i think sometimes some things can go out of control ,so its good to always have alternatives .\ni would probably hold two location one as an alternative ."
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "i would try making space for the maximum pos"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponsors play an important role in any event.\nits necessary for us to satisfy both the event audience and at same time fulfill the requirement the sponsors.\nBut that doesn't mean we have to compromise alot inorder to satisfy the sponsors .\nso its important to see if the requirments of the sponsor are well under our capabilities\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "I'll try convincing the company A for another event because its important for us to develop link with more number of sponsors.\nand at the same we shouldn't lose the existing one.\nso i would invite speaker from company B"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "creative and unique ideas would attract more audiences and at the same time i feel its essential to make us standout alone compared to others"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "I'll try doing both but if the chapter's work is soo urgent that it has to be dealt with then i'll try attending it first "
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I would appolizise to the students and make them an offer for our next event by giving some possible benefits "
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I would organize them beforehand and make the event in which i am not going to be there is well dealt with by making sure i do my part beforehand "
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "If they are strong that point and if its going to be just 3 of us then i would go with wat they are saying cuz i believe if they both are agreeing on it then it should be better than my point"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608472889477
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the primary function of a critique of your design? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            To improve the overall design. "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608474176770
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "ITS THE PROCESS OF REPEATING SOMETHING USING THE REQUIRED LOOP OR FUNCTION"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "IT CAN NOT BE CALLED."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608475294271
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608471379268
      },
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608474010964
      },
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608474188891
      }
    ],
    "username": "niranjan.venkatesan2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 7358543455,
    "first_name": "NIRANJAN",
    "last_name": "VENKATESAN",
    "registration": "19BCE0569"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "I have just started to use photoshop and filmora and I want to improve my skills in it by joining in this chapter"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "in a jpg image due to loss compressions some image data will be lost where as in an png there will not be any loss in data "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the use of pen tab in illustrator?\n ",
            "answer": "I have not yet started to illustrator so i really dont know the answer but I will learn it as quickly as possible "
          },
          {
            "question": "State types of brushes in brush tool in illustrator. ",
            "answer": "I only know 2 of the brush tools art and pattern brushes"
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "in Photoshop we can merge layers by choosing layers>merge layers"
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "well I have just started to learn about designing recently (during lockdown) and it was really interesting to do so I hope to improve my skills and learn new things by joining in the design team.\n\nI would design it in a way it will look cool and at the same time a bit easy to do or else I  will also get the help of some of my team mates in the design devision"
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "to say the truth I am a person who gets exited when some one entrust me with a work and I will pore my whole heart to do the work if its really stressful I will just listen to music and do it with my full concentration."
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608472848738
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "How would you rate your writing skills on a scale of 1 to 10 and why? ",
            "answer": "4"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608472900897
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "1. conducting any small informal events and advertising our main events during that meet\n2. creating a catchy video or a poster and sharing it in social media\n3.creating hype for the event throw different posts"
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I will try to get me work with me by influencing him without any authority "
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "I will stop my imagination (joke) i will try to see if there is any vacant rooms near the auditorium and gather all the participants and engage them in some kind of activities so that they dont know the real prob and make then engage in there for the time and will start to look for another auditorium. \n\nI will triple check all the things before confirming with good coordination"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I will try to adjust the members seats and make shifts for the event so that this problem does not occur"
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "sponsors boost the advertising the event \nfactors:\ntrustable \nsuitable for our event\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "company b as they know how to develop a company from scratch "
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "sometimes creative some times unique it depents on the event and our resources "
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "posters and videos"
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "paper due\nchapter \nurgent word (depents on the urgency)"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608474981671
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608471372622
      },
      {
        "domain": "editorial",
        "startTime": 1608472861585
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608473478731
      }
    ],
    "username": "nirajanalagappan.v2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 6,
    "contact_number": 9710511100,
    "first_name": "V Niranjan",
    "last_name": "Alagappan",
    "registration": "19MIS0055"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "Recursion is where a function calls itself.Its another way of iterating a set of code"
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "Yes it can be.\nPrivate functions can the accessed only from inside the class in which it is defined.\nProtected variables can be accessed inside a class or and inheriting class\n"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608472765556
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608471690403
      }
    ],
    "username": "sabarishsundaram.m2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 7892602892,
    "first_name": "Sabarish Sundaram",
    "last_name": "M",
    "registration": "20BCE2055"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "Why is it common to use an external power supply to drive a servo? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Servo needs more voltage than a microcontroller can provide "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "using a thinner wire and increasing the length."
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "gnd pins are used as ground or reference node"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "gyroscope, gps , accelerometer"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608472481159
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608471862864
      }
    ],
    "username": "shouvik.mukherjee2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9330771943,
    "first_name": "shouvik",
    "last_name": "mukherjee",
    "registration": "20BML0027"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the primary function of a critique of your design? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            To improve the overall design. "
          },
          {
            "question": "RGB is to ppi as CMYK is to _.\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Dots per inch "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have any experience in designing (can be Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video\nEditing, etc.)? If yes, what are the software's you have used for it? ",
            "answer": "Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe After Effects, Adobe Lightroom, Wondershare Filmora, Camtasia"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the difference between png and jpg images? ",
            "answer": "JPG compress the image where reuse could result in loss of quality. Whereas PNG won't compress it where reuse can be possible without loss of quality."
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the use of pen tab in illustrator?\n ",
            "answer": "The artists can make use of it to deliver precision results well those controls are optimized to work with Adobe illustrator to speed workflow."
          },
          {
            "question": "State types of brushes in brush tool in illustrator. ",
            "answer": "Calligraphic Brush, Scatter Brush, Art Brush, Pattern Brush, Bristle Brush"
          },
          {
            "question": "How will you merge two layers? ",
            "answer": "Holding the ctrl(Windows) or Command(Mac OS) and selecting the names of the layers or groups that I want to merge."
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you want to join design team? How would you do design if we need the\ndesign urgently? ",
            "answer": "To explore my skills and to have my own creativity to be showcased. I will go with the templates which are already created by others and posted in websites like freepik.com, stock.adobe.com can get the raw file which is .eps(Encapsulated PostScript) format can be edited and added to our wish if design is needed in urgent."
          },
          {
            "question": "How would you motivate yourself to do work when you're not in the mood to meet\nthe deadlines? ",
            "answer": "I could simply start by creating an empty file and saving it with the project name. So, whenever I get interested I will work on it little and little and will finish them before the deadline meets."
          },
          {
            "question": "Attach any of your previous work (at least 1) in the attachment below. (can be Event\nposters, Graphic designing, UI/UX, Video Editing, etc.) [ADD A DRIVE LINK] ",
            "answer": "https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1zKYIZUF_YeObyM530Zd5lOUnWvlq4sM0?usp=sharing"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608473627568
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608472412293
      }
    ],
    "username": "azgar.2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 6379916814,
    "first_name": "AZGAR",
    "last_name": "S",
    "registration": "20BCA0035"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "correctAnswers": [],
        "submittedTime": 1608472740501
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "design",
        "startTime": 1608472655118
      }
    ],
    "username": "roshnipriya.s2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 6385863772,
    "first_name": "Roshni ",
    "last_name": "Priya S",
    "registration": "20BCE2184"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a valid key for a python dictionary? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            List "
          },
          {
            "question": "Let’s say we have two different classes Car and Truck. Both the classes have a function having the same name: printInfo().\n\nclass Car:\n\t\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\t\tprint “Car model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\n\n\nclass Truck:\n\tprintInfo()\n\t{\n\tprint “Truck model is: ” //print some info\n}\n\ncarObj = Car()\ncarObj.printInfo()   //car info gets printed\ntruckObj = Truck()\ntruckObj.printInfo()  //truck info gets printed\n\n\nThe appropriate function gets called according to the object which is calling it (despite multiple functions having the same name). Which concept of OOP is used here?  ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Polymorphism "
          },
          {
            "question": ". l1= [1,2,[3,4],[[5,6],[7,8,9]],10]\n\nConsider the python list given above. What is the code to print 9 from the above list from the options given below. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            print(l1[-2][-1][2]) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            -18 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be the output of following Python code?\ndef func():\nj=10;\nprint(j++)\nfunc() ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Compile time error "
          },
          {
            "question": "Given the string, “abcdefghij”, how many possible subsequences can you form out of the given string.\nNote:  A Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some or no elements without changing the order of the remaining elements including a Null string.\nExample: Example: ‘bde’ is a substring but ‘bed’ is noT ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1024 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Can a private function call a protected variable? If yes then specify. ",
            "answer": "Yes. "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608474196187
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608472993536
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608474240540
      }
    ],
    "username": "anoushkachakravorty.a2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 8369866141,
    "first_name": "Anoushka",
    "last_name": "Chakravorty",
    "registration": "20BCE0626"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "no"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "By increasing the temperature of the circuit."
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "they are needed to connect wires"
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "ESP"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "motion sensors ,proximity sensor, light sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608474761984
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608473933866
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608474780336
      }
    ],
    "username": "rahul.d2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 9780961322,
    "first_name": "Rahul",
    "last_name": "Dinesh",
    "registration": "20BEC0387"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "What is the correct expression that will evaluate to 27.2? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2+9*((3*12)-8)/10 "
          },
          {
            "question": "j=?\nk=?\nfor i in range(2,k):\n     k-=j\n     print(k)\nWhat should be the value of k and j (respectively) so that this loop runs 7 times?\n ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9,1 "
          },
          {
            "question": "lis = ['IETE','Recruitment',5]\nfor i in range(lis.len()):\n      k=i+5\n      for j in range(k):\n           print(j)\n   How many errors can you spot in this code? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            2 "
          },
          {
            "question": "a=5\nb=\"IETE\"\nc=\"ISF\"\ni)a+b\nii)b+c\niii)a+c\nWhich of the above operations are correct? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ii only "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the below code used to print the odd number between 0 to 10? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            for i in range(0,10):\n\tif(i%2!=0):\n\t\tprint(i) "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the following statements?\nprint(.1+.2==.3)\nprint(.3==.3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            False,True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What will be stored in list1 and list2 if the following code is executed?\nList1=[‘a’,’b’,’c’]\nList1+=’de’\nList2=[1,2,3,4]\nList2+=10 ",
            "answer": "\n                                            [‘a’,’b’,’c’,’d’,’e’],error "
          },
          {
            "question": " Will the following code raise any error,if so what is the reason for the error, otherwise what is the output?\ndef what_is_required_score():\n    while score < 50:\n        score += 10\n    return score\nprint(what_is_required_score()) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Yes,Failure to initialize variable "
          },
          {
            "question": "#include <stdio.h>\n    int main() {\n        int score=10;\n\t Int pay;\n        switch (score) {\n            case 10:\n               pay=20;\n            case 20:\n                pay=30;\n      \n            case 30:\n                pay=40;\n                break;\n            default:\n                printf(\"Out of range\");\n                break;\n        }\n\tprintf(\"%d\",pay);\n        return 0;\n    } ",
            "answer": "\n                                            40 "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output for this snippet:\nint d =0;\ndef calc(a,b):\n      c = a + b\n      d = c\n      int e = d + c\n      c = a + b\n\nprint(calc(5,8))\nprint(calc(2,-1)) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            None of the above "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the output of the code given below:\n    \ndef func(x):\n    \n    if(x!=0):\n        func(x-1)\n        print(x, end=’ ’)\nfunc(3) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1 2 3 "
          },
          {
            "question": " Identify the data type in the given Line of Code? Will it give any error on running?  L = (1, 23, ‘hello’, 1) ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Tuple, Yes "
          },
          {
            "question": " Given a string s = “        IETE Recruitments 2020”, which of the following codes are incorrect or may not affect the output at all?\n\n\n1. s[1] = ‘r’\n2. print s.lower()\n3. print s[0]\n4. print s.strip(\"I\") ",
            "answer": "\n                                            1,4 "
          },
          {
            "question": " What is recursion? Explain in your own words. ",
            "answer": "calling the same function again and again inside the "
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608475265964
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "cse",
        "startTime": 1608474062006
      }
    ],
    "username": "arkajit.datta2019@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9493546827,
    "first_name": "Arkajit",
    "last_name": "Datta",
    "registration": "19BCI0115"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "Making them aware by sending mails, messages on whatsapp and regularly updating instagram handles\nIntiating close freinds to start joining these events and they would further encourage other students\nBy announcing some exciting price winning awards and trophies\n "
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I would encourage and motivate my teammate to do his work\ni would constantly guide him towards the right path of following our responsibility"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "First i would calm myself and my team\nThen would analyse the situation\nI would try to cut short the event and would only display its main objective for which the people have gathered\nI would ask other team to cooperate  as well\nFor no such further instances I would check all the meeting and appointments before the schduled time \ni would regularly follow on all event details\nwould take care of other people so that they do not commit mistakes\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I would urge people to co operate and would try to give space of volunteers sittingto audience\nalso no reservation of the seats would be allowed\nSome young people could also be asked to sit on the ground mattress "
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponrsorships are an integral part \nI would pitch my idea to those people who have an idea of the event we are going to organize so that they can understand our requirements\n\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "The new comer guy would have extra dedication towards his  new responsibilty'\nhe would be truly motivated by doing such kind of work and would have the necessary motivation"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "it is necesary for idea to be unique that will only develop interests in new kind of  exposure for the aundience"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "By putting their banners\nwearing constumes with their logo printed on it\ntime to time announcement of their of their names "
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "I would prioritize the clubs work and try to finish it fast as possible but not neglecting it\nI would first finish clubs work and then would directly go to study instead of wasting time"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I would urge people to cooperate and tell them the right exact situation\nI would organize some other kind of engaging activity for them so as to make them utilize their time\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I am only planning to join one club with full dedication and motivation"
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "we will try to negotiate and arrive at a reasonable outcome\nI would explain them my point of view and see them through my POV"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608478527255
      },
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "Making them aware by sending mails, messages on whatsapp and regularly updating instagram handles\nIntiating close freinds to start joining these events and they would further encourage other students\nBy announcing some exciting price winning awards and trophies\n "
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I would encourage and motivate my teammate to do his work\ni would constantly guide him towards the right path of following our responsibility"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "First i would calm myself and my team\nThen would analyse the situation\nI would try to cut short the event and would only display its main objective for which the people have gathered\nI would ask other team to cooperate  as well\nFor no such further instances I would check all the meeting and appointments before the schduled time \ni would regularly follow on all event details\nwould take care of other people so that they do not commit mistakes\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I would urge people to co operate and would try to give space of volunteers sittingto audience\nalso no reservation of the seats would be allowed\nSome young people could also be asked to sit on the ground mattress "
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponrsorships are an integral part \nI would pitch my idea to those people who have an idea of the event we are going to organize so that they can understand our requirements\n\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "The new comer guy would have extra dedication towards his  new responsibilty'\nhe would be truly motivated by doing such kind of work and would have the necessary motivation"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "it is necesary for idea to be unique that will only develop interests in new kind of  exposure for the aundience"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "By putting their banners\nwearing constumes with their logo printed on it\ntime to time announcement of their of their names "
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "I would prioritize the clubs work and try to finish it fast as possible but not neglecting it\nI would first finish clubs work and then would directly go to study instead of wasting time"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I would urge people to cooperate and tell them the right exact situation\nI would organize some other kind of engaging activity for them so as to make them utilize their time\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I am only planning to join one club with full dedication and motivation"
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "we will try to negotiate and arrive at a reasonable outcome\nI would explain them my point of view and see them through my POV"
          },
          {
            "question": " In this current pandemic situation, It is difficult to approach students directly to advertise our events. Suggest any three innovative methods to grab the attention of the students and publicize our events. ",
            "answer": "Making them aware by sending mails, messages on whatsapp and regularly updating instagram handles\nIntiating close freinds to start joining these events and they would further encourage other students\nBy announcing some exciting price winning awards and trophies\n "
          },
          {
            "question": " Being in a team of many members, how would you deal if one of your team members doesn’t want to work with you? ",
            "answer": "I would encourage and motivate my teammate to do his work\ni would constantly guide him towards the right path of following our responsibility"
          },
          {
            "question": " Imagine you are appointed as the event coordinator for a particular event. This is a really big event with many important people attending it, so you have booked the auditorium for the particular day and have everything sorted out. But on the morning of the event you come to know that there was some confusion and the auditorium has been assigned to two different events on the same day. It is 8:00 in the morning and your event starts at 9:30 am. How will you handle this situation? Also what necessary steps will you take beforehand to make sure something like this never happens? ",
            "answer": "First i would calm myself and my team\nThen would analyse the situation\nI would try to cut short the event and would only display its main objective for which the people have gathered\nI would ask other team to cooperate  as well\nFor no such further instances I would check all the meeting and appointments before the schduled time \ni would regularly follow on all event details\nwould take care of other people so that they do not commit mistakes\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " Suppose you are managing an offline event and the number of registrations exceeds the capacity of the assigned venue. How do you plan on smoothly conducting the event in such a case? ",
            "answer": "I would urge people to co operate and would try to give space of volunteers sittingto audience\nalso no reservation of the seats would be allowed\nSome young people could also be asked to sit on the ground mattress "
          },
          {
            "question": " Why do you think sponsors are crucial for an event. What key factors will you keep in mind to decide whether to approach an organization for sponsorships or not? ",
            "answer": "Sponrsorships are an integral part \nI would pitch my idea to those people who have an idea of the event we are going to organize so that they can understand our requirements\n\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "Company A: Well established, very famous.\nCompany B: A new start-up which is growing rapidly\nAll this while for our major events, we have been getting speakers from company A, but this we get a chance to invite a speaker from company B. From which company would you get the speaker? Why?  ",
            "answer": "The new comer guy would have extra dedication towards his  new responsibilty'\nhe would be truly motivated by doing such kind of work and would have the necessary motivation"
          },
          {
            "question": " Is it necessary to come up with an unique or creative idea to organize an event or would you choose to follow a standard procedure of going about it? ",
            "answer": "it is necesary for idea to be unique that will only develop interests in new kind of  exposure for the aundience"
          },
          {
            "question": " What are the ways in which you can publicize the sponsors product/service (if any) in online or offline mode? ",
            "answer": "By putting their banners\nwearing constumes with their logo printed on it\ntime to time announcement of their of their names "
          },
          {
            "question": " How will you prioritize work between chapter’s urgent work and a paper due tomorrow? ",
            "answer": "I would prioritize the clubs work and try to finish it fast as possible but not neglecting it\nI would first finish clubs work and then would directly go to study instead of wasting time"
          },
          {
            "question": "You are the coordinator for an event. The speaker has backed off at the last moment, due to a medical emergency. 100+ participants are waiting for him to arrive. How will you handle the situation?  ",
            "answer": "I would urge people to cooperate and tell them the right exact situation\nI would organize some other kind of engaging activity for them so as to make them utilize their time\n"
          },
          {
            "question": " If you are a part of more than one club/chapter, and are having multiple meetings at the same time.What would you do in such a situation? ",
            "answer": "I am only planning to join one club with full dedication and motivation"
          },
          {
            "question": " You along with 2 other members are given the duty to conduct a workshop. The other 2 members and you do not agree on some point. What will you do in this situation? ",
            "answer": "we will try to negotiate and arrive at a reasonable outcome\nI would explain them my point of view and see them through my POV"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608478529785
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "management",
        "startTime": 1608477057805
      }
    ],
    "username": "prajjwal.chamaria2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 3,
    "contact_number": 9660158671,
    "first_name": "Prajjwal",
    "last_name": "Chamaria",
    "registration": "20BCE0948"
  },
  {
    "correctAnswers": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "correctAnswers": [
          {
            "question": "To add a 1-second delay in the execution of your code, which among the following would you use? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            delay(1000) "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true for microcontrollers and microprocessors? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both contain processing unit "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following sensors can be used to measure distance? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Both a and b "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino can be programmed using which language? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            C Languages "
          },
          {
            "question": "Electrons would travel faster across a thicker conductor rather than a thinner conductor ",
            "answer": "\n                                            True "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the microcontroller used in Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            ATMEGA328P "
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the standard baud rate communication with the Serial Monitor that is used for Arduino Uno? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            9600 "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a 6 band color code of a resistor, what does the 6th band represent? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Temperature Coefficient "
          },
          {
            "question": "In a transistor, the base current is about ………….. of the emitter current. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            5% "
          },
          {
            "question": "When transistors are used in digital circuits they usually operate in\nthe …………. ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Saturation and cutoff regions "
          },
          {
            "question": "Arduino IDE consists of 2 functions. What are they? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Setup() and loop() "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which among the following is true? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            Microcontrollers contain a processor inside them "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of the following is considered a Universal Gate? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            NAND Gate "
          },
          {
            "question": "Which IC is considered to be a TIMER IC? ",
            "answer": "\n                                            555 "
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you need to import a library in your sketch to use an Ultrasonic sensor? If yes, mention which library. ",
            "answer": "No library is required for general sensors. Though we can still use the HCSR04 ultrasonic library to get the distance in various formats. Else we have to manually code it by sending a pulse through echo pin and detect the reflected wave by the trig pin of the sensor.\n"
          },
          {
            "question": "How can you increase the resistance in a circuit without using a resistor? ",
            "answer": "Using Longer and Thicker wires. Or we can use a rheostat."
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do you need GND pins in an Arduino board? ",
            "answer": "To provide the reference voltage to various sensors and actuators."
          },
          {
            "question": "What would you use to enable Wi-Fi communication in an Arduino system? ",
            "answer": "ESP8266, ESP32 based modules"
          },
          {
            "question": " When using a Bluetooth module with Arduino, _______ pins must be free while the code is being uploaded. ",
            "answer": "TX and RX pins of the serial communication. it can be the 0 and 1 digital pin of Arduino or any other pin using software serial"
          },
          {
            "question": " Mention any three sensors that is used in your mobile phone ",
            "answer": "Accelerometer and Gyro sensors\nAmbient Sensors\nCapacitive Touch Sensors\nInternal Temperature Sensor"
          }
        ],
        "submittedTime": 1608483199430
      }
    ],
    "startTime": [
      {
        "domain": "ece",
        "startTime": 1608482005460
      }
    ],
    "username": "shaurya.chandra2020@vitstudent.ac.in",
    "__v": 2,
    "contact_number": 9650053195,
    "first_name": "Shaurya",
    "last_name": "Chandra",
    "registration": "20BEE0314"
  }
]
